<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="URGENT BUSINESS OFFER" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="&quot;malcom tutu&quot; &lt;macontu028@yahoo.com&gt; " />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="malcom tutu &lt;macontu028@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="O" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="macontu028@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2003-02-11T00:44:37Z" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="R@S " />
<meta name="Message-To" content="R@S" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;us-ascii&quot; " />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="R@S " />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="O" />
<meta name="MboxParser-reply-to" content="macontu029@yahoo.com " />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Reply-To" content="macontu029@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="URGENT BUSINESS OFFER" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;200302091543.KAA21573@changeofhabit.mr.itd.UM&gt; " />
<meta name="creator" content="&quot;malcom tutu&quot; &lt;macontu028@yahoo.com&gt; " />
<meta name="creator" content="malcom tutu &lt;macontu028@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;us-ascii&quot;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="&quot;malcom tutu&quot; &lt;macontu028@yahoo.com&gt; " />
<meta name="meta:author" content="malcom tutu &lt;macontu028@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2003-02-11T00:44:37Z" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;us-ascii&quot; " />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2003-02-11T00:44:37Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;macontu028@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-mailer" content="Microsoft Outlook Express 5.00.2919.6900 DM or through my telephone +874-762919-885=2E" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Sun Feb  9 10:44:32 2003" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;macontu028@yahoo.com&gt; " />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-Id" content="&lt;200302091543.KAA21573@changeofhabit.mr.itd.UM&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0 " />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="malcom tutu" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="&quot;malcom tutu&quot; &lt;macontu028@yahoo.com&gt; " />
<meta name="Author" content="malcom tutu &lt;macontu028@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Mailer" content="Microsoft Outlook Express 5.00.2919.6900 DM" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-106" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="malcom tutu &lt;macontu028@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;200302091543.KAA21573@changeofhabit.mr.itd.UM&gt; " />
<title>URGENT BUSINESS OFFER</title>
</head>
<body><p>From: Mr. MALCOM TUTU  (chief auditor)
155 president street, Johannesburg,
South Africa.
Tel: +874-762919-885.
Fax:+874-762919-886.
Dear ,

Though I know that a transaction of this magnitude will make any one
apprehensive and worried, but I am assuring you that everything will
be well at the end of the day. We have decided to contact you due to
the urgency of this transaction.I got your email address while searching
for a trustworthy individual.

Let me start by introducing myself properly to you.I am Mr. malcom tutu     ,
an auditor with Ned Credict Bank, Johannesburg, South Africa .

MY  PROPOSITION:
A Foreigner a french, Late Engr.Peter Claude  (Snr) a merchant in
The Republic of South Africa, Formerly working in  Witwatersrand Johannesburg Gold Mine, Johannesburg South Africa
until his death few year ago in Kenya Air Bus (A310 - 304)Flight KQ431,
He banked with us at Ned Credict Bank Johannesburg and had a closing
balance as at the end of September, 2000 worth $30,800.000.00 (Thirty
Million eight hundred United State Dollars), (this is aside the accrued
interest so far from that date) the bank now expects his next of kin
as beneficiary. Valuable efforts are being made by the Bank to get in
touch with any of the Claude's Family or Relatives but to no success.
Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his
next of kin to come over and claim his money because we cannot release
it unless somebody applies for it as next of kin or relation to the
deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines but unfortunately we
learnt that all his supposed next of kin or relation died alongside
with him at the plane crash leaving nobody behind for the claim.

It is because of the perceived possibility of not being able to locate
any of Late Engr. Peter Claude (Snr.)'s next of kin . The Management
under the influence of our Chairman and Members of the Board of
Directors, Thus that arrangement will be made for the fund to be decleared
"Unclaimed" and subsequentlly be donated to the trust fund for arms and
ammunition to further enhance the course of War in Africa and the World
in General.

In order to avert this negative development, some of my trusted
colleagues and I, now seek your permission to have you stand as next of
kin to the late Engr.peter Claude  (Snr.) so that the fund will be
released and paid into your Account as the beneficiary/next of kin.
The request of  foreigner as next of kin in this business is occasioned
by the fact that the customer(Claude) was a foreigner and a Local person here
in the country  cannot stand as next of kin to a foreigner.


All documents and proves to enable you get this fund will be carefully
worked out. We have secured from the probate registry, an order of
Mandamus to locate any of the deceased's beneficiary(ies), and more so
we are assuring you that this business is 100% Risk Free. Your share
will be 30% of the total sum while 10% will be set aside for any
expences incured during the course of transaction, The rest of 60% will
be for myself and my colleagues for investment purposes, According to
agreement between both parties.

Therefore to enable the immediate trnansfer of this fund to you as
arranged, you must apply first to the bank as relations or next of kin
of the deceased indicating your bank name, your bank account number,
your private telephone and fax number for easy and effective
communication and location where-in the money will be remitted . I will
also instruct you on how you can add in your application to our bank so
that you get paid through our corresponding bank  overseas as this will
be easier for us. Upon receipt of your reply, I will send to you by
fax or email the text of the application.

Please note that for the purposes of confidentiality, all further
correspondeces would be through my alternative email address:macontu5@consultant.com
 or through my telephone +874-762919-885.

Accept my warm regards as I await your response.

Sincerely,

malcom tutu



</p>

</body></html>