<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Disposition-Notification-To" content="&lt;taofeekmarvin@netscape.net&gt;" />
<meta name="subject" content=" Assistant." />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="taofeekmarvin@netscape.net" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="taofeekmarvin@netscape.net" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2004-08-23T12:59:32Z" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="taofeekmarvin@netscape.net" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="R@M" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="R@M" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="R@M" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="dc:title" content=" Assistant." />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;200408231259.i7NCwuA3007839@cryforhelp.mr.itd.UM&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="taofeekmarvin@netscape.net" />
<meta name="creator" content="taofeekmarvin@netscape.net" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="taofeekmarvin@netscape.net" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="taofeekmarvin@netscape.net" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2004-08-23T12:59:32Z" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2004-08-23T12:59:32Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;taofeekmarvin@netscape.net&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-priority" content="3" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Priority" content="3" />
<meta name="MboxParser-disposition-notification-to" content="&lt;taofeekmarvin@netscape.net&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Mon Aug 23 08:59:45 2004" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;taofeekmarvin@netscape.net&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-Id" content="&lt;200408231259.i7NCwuA3007839@cryforhelp.mr.itd.UM&gt;" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="taofeekmarvin@netscape.net" />
<meta name="Author" content="taofeekmarvin@netscape.net" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-1089" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="taofeekmarvin@netscape.net" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;200408231259.i7NCwuA3007839@cryforhelp.mr.itd.UM&gt;" />
<title> Assistant.</title>
</head>
<body><p>Dear friend,

I am Mr Taofeek Marvin  a native of cape town in south
Africa and I am an Executive Accountant with the
south Africa ministry of mineral resources and
energy.

I have decided to seek a confidential co-operation
with you in the execution of a deal described here
under for the benefit of all parties and I hope you we
keep it as a top secret because of the nature of this
transaction.

Within the department of mining and natural resources
where I work as an accountant and with the
co-operation of four other top officials we have in
our possession an over due payment bills totally
Twelve million five hundred thousand united state
dollars($12.5m) which we want to transfer abroad with
the assistance and co-operation of a foreign 
company/individual to receive such funds, also we are
handicapped in the circumstances as the south Africa
civil code of conduct does not allow us to operate
off-shore account hence your importance in the whole
transaction.

This amount represent the balance of the total
contract value executed on behalf of my department
contraction firm which we the officials over-invoiced
deliberately.

Though the actual contract cost have been paid to the
original contractors, leaving the balances in the tune
of the said amount which we have in principles gotten
approval to remit by Key Tested Telegraphic Transfer
(K .T.T) to any foreign bank you we provide by
filling an application through the justice ministry
here in south Africa for the transfer of rights and
privileges of former contractors to you.

I have the authority of my partners involved to
proposed that, should you be willing to assist us in
the transaction, your share of the sum we be 25% of
the total sum, 70% for us and 5% for taxation and
other expenses .I we like to inform you that the
transaction of this deal is save there is nothing to
fear about.Provided you treat it with utmost
secrecy and confidentiality on your part. Also your
area of specialization is not a hindrance to the
successful execution of this transaction. I have all
my confidence and trust in you and I hope you we not
disappoint me.

I am on a year study leave here in Europe.
Content me if you are in interested in this deal and
also if you are not to enable me know my stand.

I and my partners are in position to make the payment
of this funds possible provided you can assure us the
safety of our share.

Please remember to treat this matter confidentially
because we are still in service and remember once
again that time is important in this business.

I wait in anticipation for your full co-operation.

Accept my special regards.

Taofeek Marvin
taofeekmarvin@netscape.net



</p>

</body></html>