<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Spam-Status" content="No -- Hits: 3.197  Required: 5" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-scanned-by" content="MIMEDefang 2.42" />
<meta name="subject" content="RE:INQUIRY" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="fwilliams23us@tiscali.it" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="fwilliams23us@tiscali.it" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-spam-summary" content="BAYES_00,NIGERIAN_BODY1,NIGERIAN_BODY2,NIGERIAN_BODY3,NIGERIAN_BODY4,NO_REAL_NAME,UNDISC_RECIPS,US_DOLLARS_3" />
<meta name="MboxParser-http" content="//abbonati.tiscali.it/adsl/" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="fwilliams23us@tiscali.it" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;iso-8859-1&quot;" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="&lt;R@E&gt;" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="R@E" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="R@E" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-spam-status" content="No -- Hits: 3.197  Required: 5" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Scanned-By" content="MIMEDefang 2.42" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Spam-Summary" content="BAYES_00,NIGERIAN_BODY1,NIGERIAN_BODY2,NIGERIAN_BODY3,NIGERIAN_BODY4,NO_REAL_NAME,UNDISC_RECIPS,US_DOLLARS_3" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="RE:INQUIRY" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="creator" content="fwilliams23us@tiscali.it" />
<meta name="creator" content="fwilliams23us@tiscali.it" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;iso-8859-1&quot;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="fwilliams23us@tiscali.it" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="fwilliams23us@tiscali.it" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;iso-8859-1&quot;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;fwilliams23us@tiscali.it&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Wed Sep 22 13:14:15 2004" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;fwilliams23us@tiscali.it&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="fwilliams23us@tiscali.it" />
<meta name="Author" content="fwilliams23us@tiscali.it" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-1146" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="fwilliams23us@tiscali.it" />
<title>RE:INQUIRY</title>
</head>
<body><p>Good day,

It is my humble pleasure to write this letter irrespective of the fact that
you do not know me. However, I came to know of you in my private search
for a reliable and trustworthy person that can handle a confidential transaction
of this nature in respect of this, I got your contact through an uprooted
search on the internet. Though I know that a transaction of this magnitude
will make any one apprehensive and worried, but I am assuring you that allwill
be well at the end of the day.

I am Frank Williams, son of late Dr John Williams of Sierra Leone who was
killed by the Sierra Leone's rebel forces on the 24th of December,1999 in
my country Sierra Leone.
When he was still alive, he deposited one trunk box containing the sum of
US$10,000,000.00 with one private security and safe deposit company and
declared the box as containing African Artwork for export to a foreign partner.

This money was made from the sale of Gold and Diamond and he already decided
to use this money for future investment of the family before he died.Recently,
I rushed down to Abidjan after being able to locate where my late father
kept the depository agreement and the certificate of deposit that was given
to him by the security company when he deposited the consignment in their
custody.
I have confirmed from the security company that the consignment is with
them, when I demanded for the release of the consignment to me in my capacity
of being the son of Dr Williams, the depositor of the consignment, I was
told that in the absence of my father, the only person that can demand for
the funds is my late father?s foreign partner on whose behalf the consignment
was deposited.

When my late father deposited the consignment, he did not give the name
or gender of his foreign partner on whose behalf he was depositing the consignment,
he made the declaration for security reasons as he did not want the securitycompany
to inspect the contents of the consignment hence he declared thebox as belonging
to his foreign partner.
Meanwhile, my father have instructed me that in the case of his death, that
I should look for a trusted foreigner who can assist me to move out thismoney
from Côte d'Ivoire immediately for investment .
Based on this , I solicit for your assistance to retrieve and transfer this
fund into your Account, but I will demand from you if you could be able
to introduce me to a profitable business venture that would not require
much technical expertise in your country where this fund will be invested?

I am a Christian and I will please, want you to handle this transactionbased
on the trust I have established on you. For your assistance in thistransaction,
I have decided to compensate you with 10 percent of the total amount at
the end of this business.
The security of this business is very important to me and as such, I wouldlike
you to keep this business very confidential.

I shall expect an early response from you.
Thank you and God bless.
Yours sincerely,
Frank Williams
This message may contain confidential and/or privileged information. If
you are not the addressee or authorized to receive this for the addressee,
you must not use, copy, disclose or take any action based on this message
or any information herein.
Thank you for your cooperation



__________________________________________________________________
Tiscali Adsl 640 Free: fino al 15 novembre i consumi sono GRATIS!
Se sottoscrivi un'Adsl Free 640 entro il 30 settembre avrai gratis tutti
i consumi fino al 15/11/04 compreso! In piu' sono gratis il modem in comodato
e l'attivazione. Cosa aspetti? Prima attivi, piu' risparmi. Attivala subito!
http://abbonati.tiscali.it/adsl/





</p>

</body></html>