<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="REQUEST FOR ASSISTANCE!!!" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="&quot;Dr Peter Akinjide&quot; &lt;peterakinjide40@tiscali.it&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="Dr Peter Akinjide &lt;peterakinjide40@tiscali.it&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-http" content="//abbonati.tiscali.it/adsl/" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="O" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="peterakinjide40@tiscali.it" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="peterakinjide40@tiscali.it" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="peterakinjide40@tiscali.it" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;iso-8859-1&quot;" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="peterakinjide40@tiscali.it" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="O" />
<meta name="MboxParser-reply-to" content="peterakinjide70@tiscali.it" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="REQUEST FOR ASSISTANCE!!!" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Reply-To" content="peterakinjide70@tiscali.it" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="creator" content="&quot;Dr Peter Akinjide&quot; &lt;peterakinjide40@tiscali.it&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="Dr Peter Akinjide &lt;peterakinjide40@tiscali.it&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;iso-8859-1&quot;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="&quot;Dr Peter Akinjide&quot; &lt;peterakinjide40@tiscali.it&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="Dr Peter Akinjide &lt;peterakinjide40@tiscali.it&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;iso-8859-1&quot;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;peterakinjide40@tiscali.it&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Fri Oct  1 12:06:33 2004" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;peterakinjide40@tiscali.it&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="Dr Peter Akinjide" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="&quot;Dr Peter Akinjide&quot; &lt;peterakinjide40@tiscali.it&gt;" />
<meta name="Author" content="Dr Peter Akinjide &lt;peterakinjide40@tiscali.it&gt;" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-1177" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="Dr Peter Akinjide &lt;peterakinjide40@tiscali.it&gt;" />
<title>REQUEST FOR ASSISTANCE!!!</title>
</head>
<body><p>Dr.Peter Akinjide

Ikoyi office complex,

Lagos, Nigeria.



Dear Friend,

I am Dr.Peter Akinjide,on behalf of my colleagues from different Federal
Government of Nigeria owned parastatals decided to solicit your assistance
as regards transfer of US$41,500,000.00 (Fourty one Million,five Hundred
Thousand US Dollars)into your bank account. These funds emanated from unclaimed
contractual proceeds of foreign contracting firms who could not meet their
financial obligations to their creditors. We, as holders of sensitive positions
in our various parastatals, were mandated by the Federal Government to scrutinise
all payments made to certain foreign contractors and we discovered that
some of the contractors have not been paid their contractual entitlement
which collectively left the sum of US$46,500,000.00 (Fourty six Million,five
Hundred Thousand US Dollars) lying in a suspended Account.

However,from our investigations,we discovered that the foreign beneficiary
companies have since been liquidated, and to all intents and purposes no
longer exist in Nigeria, thus providing us with this
opportunity,provided that we have a capable partner, to execute a transaction
of this nature.

We agreed that the said amount would be transferred into an overseas Bank
Account to be provided by a reliable foreign firm/associate. This is because
as serving Government workers the Civil Service Code does not allow us to
operate foreign Account. In our initial attempt to do
this,we succeeded in transferring part of this amount US$5m (Five Million
Dollars)into a United States Dollar Account in Beirut, Lebanon, but our
foreign associate failed to honour our mutual agreement insisting instead
that the total amount be transferred into the Account before we can share
the money.

As a result, we have lost confidence in the ability of our Lebanese partner
to see this matter to its logical conclusion,and until the initial transaction
is satisfactorily resolved,we have cancelled further transactions with him.In
the light of the foregoing,it is clear
that we require a partner that is not only capable of rendering assistance
and cooperation in executing this matter, but will honour the terms of agreement
when we reach the concluding stages of this transaction.

We therefore offer the amount of 20% of the entire sum in return for services/assistance
rendered in successfully carrying out this project.We trust that you appreciate
the sensitive nature of this matter and the need for initial caution on
our part, but when a relationship is confidently established and operations
commence you will be provided with all relevant information.

I remain at your disposal to entertain any questions/enquiries relating
to this proposition and you may contact me as a matter of urgency via e-mail
for further information on the procedures and requirements of this transaction.In
your reply, remember to indicate a safe telephone number where I can always
reach you. Hope to hear from you soon. Please treat with the strictest confidentiality
and expediency.

Yours faithfully,

Dr.Peter Akinjide








__________________________________________________________________
Tiscali Adsl 640 Free: fino al 15 novembre i consumi sono GRATIS!
Se sottoscrivi un'Adsl Free 640 entro il 14 ottobre avrai gratis tutti
i consumi fino al 15/11/04 compreso! In piu' sono gratis il modem
in comodato e l'attivazione. Cosa aspetti? Prima attivi, piu' risparmi!
http://abbonati.tiscali.it/adsl/





</p>

</body></html>