<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="AWAITING YOUR FAVOURABLE REPLY" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="che_pui67 &lt;che_pui67@yahoo.com.hk&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="che_pui67 &lt;che_pui67@yahoo.com.hk&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2004-12-31T20:17:29Z" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="che_pui67@yahoo.com.hk" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=us-ascii" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="AWAITING YOUR FAVOURABLE REPLY" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="7bit" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;200412312017.iBVKHTLq002660@opus07.register.it&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-rid" content="7OnsJ3MjKOhkK20vCg== Z3IrJ3RjI2orcuwtI3QlciVrJ1tbWwo= XV3gJyw9J6Oj4CfgPQo=" />
<meta name="creator" content="che_pui67 &lt;che_pui67@yahoo.com.hk&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="che_pui67 &lt;che_pui67@yahoo.com.hk&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; charset=us-ascii" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="che_pui67 &lt;che_pui67@yahoo.com.hk&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="che_pui67 &lt;che_pui67@yahoo.com.hk&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2004-12-31T20:17:29Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Mime-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=us-ascii" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2004-12-31T20:17:29Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="7bit" />
<meta name="Message-Cc" content="" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;nobody@opus07.register.it&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-mailer" content="RLSP Mailer" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-priority" content="3 (Normal)" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Priority" content="3 (Normal)" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Fri Dec 31 15:18:32 2004" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;nobody@opus07.register.it&gt; " />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-Id" content="&lt;200412312017.iBVKHTLq002660@opus07.register.it&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="che_pui67" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="che_pui67 &lt;che_pui67@yahoo.com.hk&gt;" />
<meta name="Author" content="che_pui67 &lt;che_pui67@yahoo.com.hk&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Mailer" content="RLSP Mailer" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-1346" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-RID" content="7OnsJ3MjKOhkK20vCg== Z3IrJ3RjI2orcuwtI3QlciVrJ1tbWwo= XV3gJyw9J6Oj4CfgPQo=" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="che_pui67 &lt;che_pui67@yahoo.com.hk&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;200412312017.iBVKHTLq002660@opus07.register.it&gt;" />
<title>AWAITING YOUR FAVOURABLE REPLY</title>
</head>
<body><p>
MR. CHEUNG PUI
HANG SENG BANK LTD.
DES VOEUX RD. BRANCH,
CENTRAL HONG KONG,
HONG KONG.
 

Let me start by introducing myself. I am Mr.Cheung Pui 
director of operations of the Hang Seng Bank Ltd. I 
have an urgent business suggestion for you.

I honestly apologize and hope I do not cause you much 
embarrassment by contacting you through this means for 
a transaction of this magnitude,but this is due to 
confidentiality and prompt access reposed on this 
medium.Furthermore,due to this issue on my hands 
now,it became necesary for me to seek your assistance, 
and it is imperative for me to know your opinion

Before the U.S and Iraqi war our client Major Fadi 
Bassem who was with the Iraqi forces and also business 
man made a numbered fixed deposit for 18 calendar 
months, with a value of Twenty Four millions Five Hundred Thousand United State Dollars only in my branch. Upon maturity several 
notice was sent to him, even during the war early this 
year. Again after the war  another notification was 
sent and still no response came from him. We later 
find out that the Major and his family had been killed 
during the war in bomb blast that hit their home.

After further investigation it was also discovered 
that Major Fadi Basem  did not declare any next of kin 
in his official papers including the paper work of his 
bank deposit. And he also confided in me the last time 
he was at my office that no one except me knew of his 
deposit in my bank. So, Twenty Four millions Five 
Hundred Thousand United State Dollars is still lying 
in my bank and no one will ever come forward to claim 
it. What bothers me most is that according to the laws 
of my country at the expiration 5 years the funds will 
revert to the ownership of the Hong Kong Government if 
nobody applies to claim the funds. 

Against this backdrop, my suggestion to you is that I 
will like you as a foreigner to stand as the next of 
kin to Major Fadi Basem  so that you will be able to 
receive his funds. 

WHAT IS TO BE DONE:

I want you to know that I have had everything planned 
out so that we shall come out successful. I have 
contacted an attorney that will prepare the necessary 
document that will back you up as the next of kin to Major Fadi Basem , 
all that is required from you at this stage is for you 
to provide me with your Full Names and Address so that 
the attorney can commence his job. After you have been 
made the next of kin, the attorney will also file in 
for claims on your behalf and secure the necessary 
approval and letter of probate in your favor for the 
move of the funds to an account that will be provided 
by you.

There is no risk involved at all in the matter as we 
are going to adopt a legalized method and the attorney 
will prepare all the necessary documents. Please 
endeavor to observe utmost discretion in all matters 
concerning thisissue.Once the funds have been 
transferred to your nominated bank account we shall 
share in the ratio of 70% for me, 25% for you and 5% 
for any expenses incure during the transaction. Should 
you be interested please send me your full names and 
current residential address and I will prefer you to 
reach me via my private box, 

{che_Pui67@yahoo.com.hk} and finally after that i shall provide you with more details of this operation.

Your earliest response to this letter will be 
appreciated.

Kind Regards,

Mr Cheung Pui.





















___________________________________________________________________________
Mail sent from Karate Project WebMail Service http://www.karate-project.org


</p>

</body></html>