<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="Mrs. Mary Jerry Agbeyegbe" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="mrsjerry124@handbag.com" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="mrsjerry124@handbag.com" />
<meta name="MboxParser-http" content="//www.vanguardngr.com/articles/2002/cover/f214102004.html" />
<meta name="MboxParser-http" content="//www.businessdayonline.com/index.php?fArticleId=3D4912" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="O" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="mrsjerry124@handbag.com" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;iso-8859-1&quot;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="O" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="Mrs. Mary Jerry Agbeyegbe" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="creator" content="mrsjerry124@handbag.com" />
<meta name="creator" content="mrsjerry124@handbag.com" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;iso-8859-1&quot;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="mrsjerry124@handbag.com" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="mrsjerry124@handbag.com" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;iso-8859-1&quot;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;acl-webmaster-errors@UM&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Tue Mar 15 06:21:58 2005" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;acl-webmaster-errors@UM&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="mrsjerry124@handbag.com" />
<meta name="Author" content="mrsjerry124@handbag.com" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-1501" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="mrsjerry124@handbag.com" />
<title>Mrs. Mary Jerry Agbeyegbe</title>
</head>
<body><p>Dear Sir, CEO, Managing Director?s/Madam



Please, treat this mail as urgent and important. I am Mrs. Mary Jerry Agbeyegbe.
I am the wife to the late Mr. Jerry Agbeyegbe who was the Executive director
of the Nigerian Aviation safely initiative.

I am contacting you under a bereaved condition, I hope that you will treat
this mail with special concern and reply immediately as the need is very
urgent. My husband was murdered in the fee hours of Tuesday October 12, 2004
at the Alapere end of the Oworonsoki/Third Mainland Bridge, Lagos. You can
read the following journals concerning my husband's
death.

http://www.vanguardngr.com/articles/2002/cover/f214102004.html
http://www.businessdayonline.com/index.php?fArticleId=4912

He was buried on Friday the 3rd of December 2004.I have a different problem
now, apart from my husband's death. The future of my children and I, are
in serious danger, base on circumstances around the family in relation with
the tradition of my husband's home town. We are from Aja Ojobo, Ekurede Itsekiri,
Warri of Delta state of Nigeria. The tradition of this part of Nigeria, have
it that once a man dies, the family members, are entitled to all his assets,
including the wife and kids.

This very ackward tradition has caused a lot of problems between widows,
their children and the husband's family. I am married to a family of high
integrities and respected men in this society, who I can not face physically
in terms of problems over their late brother's assets. I am civilized woman;
I will not allow a rubbish tradition to rubbish our future. Seven days after
my husband's burial, I was called before the whole family to submit documents
of my husband, including his bank accounts to the family base on this barbaric
tradition.

Base on my late husband good intension for his children, I secured one thing
which will sustain us in life. My late husband made a wise provision to make
sure that in case of death, I and the kids will not face the barbaric effect
of the useless tradition.  My husband made a deposit of us$45million with
a finance firm in Europe. Like he used to tell me


when he was alive, He told me times without number that death is inevitable,
if he is no more for us, that I must make sure I protect his kids from any
failure to bring them up in the normal way both educationally and otherwise.
He advised me to make sure I do not let his brothers get to this deposit
in his absence.

He instructed me to seek for a good foreigner that will assist me secure
the money and assist us move away from this country build up a new life.
He charged himself while he was alive that our children must have the best
of educations in life. My husband made money while he was alive and our kids
should not suffer in the hands of the family for tradition sake. It is only
for this reason that he made this secret offshore deposit outside his family
knowledge.

Already, my late husband kept the documents of this deposit in the custody
of our lawyer friend in Amsterdam-The Netherlands. So there is no way the
family will get to know this. Please base on the sensitivity of this matter,
I will please plead you to keep this as a top secret. The air they said has
ears. We may not know who is by the side.

What I need from you is your full consent to present you to the financial
firm as the beneficiary to the deposit. In this way, the finance firm will
transact with you directly as the beneficiary release the deposit to you.
Once you retrieve the fund, you will keep the money with you until we arrange
for our coming over to meet you there in your country. When we come over,
we will look for a lucrative business to invest the money.

Every other arrangements concerning this, will be after you reply to this
mail, give me your full contact detail and phone number, and private email
where the need be.  I will gladly offer you a good percentage of the money
for your kind assistance.



Note that your immediate reply is needed so that I will not look for another
person.  Thank you while I look forward to hearing from you as soon as possible.
Mrs. Mary Agbeyegbe



Pls., get back to me with this email box mragbeyejerry27@netscape.net

Best regards.

Mrs. Mary J.Agbeyegbe






___________________________________________________________

Book yourself something to look forward to in 2005.
Cheap flights - http://www.tiscali.co.uk/travel/flights/
Bargain holidays - http://www.tiscali.co.uk/travel/holidays/





___________________________________________________________

Book yourself something to look forward to in 2005.
Cheap flights - http://www.tiscali.co.uk/travel/flights/
Bargain holidays - http://www.tiscali.co.uk/travel/holidays/





</p>

</body></html>