<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="GOOD  DAY" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="&quot;MR DANIEL KALU&quot; &lt;danielkalukalu@netscape.net&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="MR DANIEL KALU &lt;danielkalukalu@netscape.net&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="O" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="danielkalukalu@netscape.net" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2003-10-04T13:17:14Z" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="R@M" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="R@M" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain;charset=&quot;iso-8859-1&quot;" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="R@M" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="O" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="GOOD  DAY" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="7bit" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;200303110518.h2B5Imr04727@perfectworld.mr.itd.UM&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="&quot;MR DANIEL KALU&quot; &lt;danielkalukalu@netscape.net&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="MR DANIEL KALU &lt;danielkalukalu@netscape.net&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain;charset=&quot;iso-8859-1&quot;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="&quot;MR DANIEL KALU&quot; &lt;danielkalukalu@netscape.net&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="MR DANIEL KALU &lt;danielkalukalu@netscape.net&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2003-10-04T13:17:14Z" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain;charset=&quot;iso-8859-1&quot;" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2003-10-04T13:17:14Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="7bit" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;danielkalukalu@netscape.net&gt;	by perfectworld.mr.itd.UM (3.6u) with SMTP id h2B5Imr04727	for &lt;R@M&gt;; Tue, 11 Mar 2003 00:18:49 -0500 (EST)" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Tue Mar 11 00:19:07 2003" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;danielkalukalu@netscape.net&gt; by perfectworld.mr.itd.UM (3.6u) with SMTP id h2B5Imr04727 for &lt;R@M&gt;; Tue, 11 Mar 2003 00:18:49 -0500 (EST)" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-Id" content="&lt;200303110518.h2B5Imr04727@perfectworld.mr.itd.UM&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="MR DANIEL KALU" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="&quot;MR DANIEL KALU&quot; &lt;danielkalukalu@netscape.net&gt;" />
<meta name="Author" content="MR DANIEL KALU &lt;danielkalukalu@netscape.net&gt;" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-151" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="MR DANIEL KALU &lt;danielkalukalu@netscape.net&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;200303110518.h2B5Imr04727@perfectworld.mr.itd.UM&gt;" />
<title>GOOD  DAY</title>
</head>
<body><p>danielkalukalu@netscape.net
kalukalu2003@ecplaza.net     


UNION BANK NIGERIA PLC
LAGOS NIGERIA
40/46 MARINA STREET LAGOS

FROM THE DESK OF DANIEL KALU
MANAGER,BILLS AND EXCHANGE.
TELEPHONE 234-8033008245
ATTN ,

REQUEST FOR BUSINESS PARTNERSHIP 

I AM THE MANAGER OF BILLS AND EXCHANGE AT THE FOREIGN REMITTANCE 
DEPARTMENT OF THIS BANK. IAM WRITING YOU FOLLOWING THE IMPRESSIVE 
INFORMATION ABOUT YOU THROUGH ONE OF MY FRIENDS WHO WORKED WITH 
THE NIGERIAN CHAMBER OF COMERCE BEFORE HIS TRANSFER TO THE NIGERIAN TRADE
MISSION IN HONG KONG. HE ASSURED ME OF YOUR CAPABILITY AND RELIABILITY 
TO CHAMPION A BUSINESS OF GREAT MAGNITUDE LIKE THIS ONE,ALTHOUGH 
I DID NOT TELL HIM THE NATURE OF THIS BUSINESS BECAUSE OF THE CONFIDENTIALITY IT REQUIRES.

IN MY DEPARTMENT, WE DISCOVERED AN ABANDONED SUM OF USD25MILLION(TWENTY 
FIVE MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS ONLY) IN A DOMICILIARY ACCOUNT 
THAT BELONGS TO ONE OF OUR FOREIGN CUSTOMERS WHO DIED IN A GHASTLY PLANE
CRASH IN JANUARY ! 2000 ABOARD KENYA AIRWAYS ALONG WITH HIS ENTIRE FAMILY.

SINCE WE GOT THE INFORMATION ABOUT HIS DEATH, WE HAVE EXPECTED HIS 
NEXT- OF- KIN TO COME OVER AND CLAIM THE MONEY BECAUSE WE CANNOT 
RELEASE IT UNLESS SOMEBODY APPLIES FOR IT AS THE NEXT OF KIN OR RELATION TO THE
DECEASED AS INDICATED IN OUR BANKING GUIDELINES. UNFORTUNATELY WE 
LEARNT THAT ALL HIS SUPPOSED NEXT OF KIN OR RELATIONS DIED ALONG 
WITH HIM AT THE PLANE CRASH LEAVING NOBODY BEHIND FOR THE CLAIM. 
IT IS UPON THIS DISCOVERY THEREFORE, THAT I AND ONE KEY OFFICIALS 
IN MY DEPARTMENT NOW DECIDED TO MAKE BUSINESS WITH YOU AND RELEASE 
THE MONEY TO YOU AS THE NEXT OF KIN OR RELATION OF THE DECEASED 
FOR SAFE-KEEPING AND SUBSEQUENT DISBURSEMENT WITH YOU SINCE NOBODY 
IS COMING FOR IT AND WE DO NOT WANT THIS MONEY TO BE RECYCLED INTO 
THE BANK'S BOUNDED ACCOUNT AS AN UNCLAIMED FUND.

THE REQUEST FOR A FOREIGNER AS NEXT OF KIN IN THIS BUSINESS IS 
OCCASIONED BY THE FAC! T THAT THE CUSTOMER WAS A FOREIGNER AND A NIGERIA 
CANNOT STAND AS NEXT OF KIN TO A FOREIGNER. WE HAVE AGREED THAT 
25% OF THIS MONEY WILL BE FOR YOU AS FOREIGN PARTNER, THEREAFTER 
MY COLLEAGUE AND I WILL VISIT YOUR COUNTRY FOR THE DISBURSEMENT 
ACCORDING TO THE AGREED PERCENTAGES.
PERSONALLY, I WOULD WANT YOU TO ADVISE ME ON THE BEST AREA OF INVESTMENT 
BECAUSE I AM CONSIDERING TO INVEST THE GREATER PROPORTION OF MY SHARE IN YOUR COUNTRY.

THEREFORE TO ENABLE THE IMMEDIATE TRANSFER OF THE FUND VIA OUR CORRESPONDENT 
FINANCE HOUSE IN ABORAD TO YOU AS ARRANGED, YOU SHOULD FIRST APPLY 
TO THE BANK AS THE NEXT OF KIN OR BUSINESS PARTNER OF THE
DECEASED INDICATING YOUR ACCOUNT DETAILS WHEREIN THE MONEY WILL 
BE REMITED. UPON RECEIPT OF YOUR REPLY MAIL, I SHALL SEND TO YOU 
THE TEXT OF THE APPLICATION WHICH YOU WILL BE REQUIRED TO SUMIT TO THE BANK FOR
THE BANK'S PROCEDURAL AUTHENTICATION AND IMMEDIATE REMITTANCE OF 
THE MONEY TO THE ! ACCOUNT YOU ARE GOING TO NOMINATE.

AS SOON AS YOU RECEIVE THIS MAIL, DO CONTACT ME AT ONCE THROUGH 
MY EMAIL mustafabello@operamail.com, AT ONCE OR BETTER STILL YOU CALL ME TELEPHONE 234-8033008245
ON MY ABOVE TELEPHONE NUMBER FOR MORE CLARIFICATION. 

AND I WOULD ALSO LIKE YOU TO INDICATE YOUR PRIVATE AND CONFIDENTIAL 
TELEPHONE, FAX,CELLULAR AND E-MAIL FOR THE EFFECTIVE COMMUNICATION REQUIRED.

*BE INFORMED THAT ALL NECESSARY ARRANGEMENTS TOWARDS THE SUCCESSFUL 
TRANSFER OF THE FUND VIA OUR CORRESPONDENT FINANCE HOUSE IN ABORAD 
HAVE BEEN CONCLUDED AND IT IS 100% RISK FREE. 


TRUSTING TO HEAR FROM YOU IMMEDIATELY.

YOURS FAITHFULLY,
MR.DANIEL KALU






</p>

</body></html>