<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="TRANSFER OF FUND" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="donmbeki@tiscali.cz" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="donmbeki@tiscali.cz" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="donmbeki@tiscali.cz" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;ISO-8859-2&quot;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="TRANSFER OF FUND" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="creator" content="donmbeki@tiscali.cz" />
<meta name="creator" content="donmbeki@tiscali.cz" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;ISO-8859-2&quot;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="donmbeki@tiscali.cz" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="donmbeki@tiscali.cz" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;ISO-8859-2&quot;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;donmbeki@tiscali.cz&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Fri Mar 18 14:02:05 2005" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;donmbeki@tiscali.cz&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="donmbeki@tiscali.cz" />
<meta name="Author" content="donmbeki@tiscali.cz" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-1516" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="donmbeki@tiscali.cz" />
<title>TRANSFER OF FUND</title>
</head>
<body><p>DEAR SIR/MADAM,
REPLY TO:   mannyfold@indiatimes.com

IN ORDER TO TRANSFER OUT ( THIRTY FIVE POINT FIVE MILLION U.S.DOLLARS)
FROM OUR BANK. I HAVE THE COURAGE TO LOOK FOR A REALIABLE AND HONEST
PERSON WHO WILL BE CAPABLE FOR THIS IMPORTANT BUSINESS. BELIEVING THAT
YOU WILL NEVER LET ME DOWN EITHER NOW OR IN FUTURE.

I AM MR DONALD MBEKI, THE AUDITOR AND COMPUTING MANAGER OF OUR BANK.
THERE IS AN ACCOUNT OPENED IN OUR BANK IN 1980 AND SINCE 1990 TILL DATE,

NOBODY HAS OPERATED ON THIS ACCOUNT AGAIN.
AFTER GOING THROUGH SOME OLD FILES IN THE RECORDS I DISCOVERED THAT IF
I DO NOT REMITT THIS MONEY OUT URGENTELY IT WILL BE FORFEITED FOR
NOTHING.

THE OWNER OF THIS ACCOUNT IS REV'D FR. CLAYTON REIDFIELD A MISSIONARY
AND HE DIED SINCE 1990. NO OTHER PERSON KNOWS ABOUT THIS ACCOUNT OR
ANYTHING CONCERNING IT, THE ACCOUNT HAS NO OTHER BENEFICIARY AND MY
INVESTIGATION PROVED TO ME AS WELL THAT HIS CHURCH DOES NOT KNOW ANYTHING

ABOUT THIS ACCOUNT AND THE AMOUNT INVLOVED IS(U.S.$35.5,000,000.00).

I WANT TO TRANSFER THIS MONEY INTO A SAFE FOREIGN ACCOUNT ABROAD BUT I
DON'T KNOW ANY FOREIGNER, I AM ONLY CONTACTING YOU AS A FOREIGNER
BECAUSE THIS MONEY CAN NOT BE APPROVED TO ANY LOCAL BANK HERE BUT CAN ONLY

BE APPROVED TO ANY FOREIGN ACCOUNT BECAUSE THE MONEY IS U.S DOLLARS AND

THE FOMER OWNER OF THE ACCOUNT IS MR CLAYTON REIDFIELD AND HE WAS A
FOREIGNER TOO.
I KNOW THAT THIS MESSAGE WILL COME TO YOU AS ASURPRISE AS WE DON'T KNOW

OURSELVES BEFORE, BUT BE SURE THAT IT IS REAL AND A GENUINE BUSINESS.

I BELIEVE IN GOD THAT YOU WILL NEVER LET ME DOWN IN THIS BUSINESS, YOU
ARE THE ONLY PERSON THAT I HAVE CONTACTED FOR THIS BUSINESS FOR NOW. SO

PLEASE REPLY URGENTLY.

WHEN THE TRANSFER IS APPROVED AND PAYMENT SCHEDULE IS ALLOCATED
OVERSEAS,THROUGH THE OFFSHORE PAYING DELEGATE FOR FINAL CLEARANCE AND SIGNING

OF THE PAYMENT REALEASE FORM BY THE BENEFICIARY, I WANT US TO SEE AT
THE OVERSEA PAYING CLEARANCE OFFICE FACE TO FACE OR SIGNING OF THE
ORIGINAL BINDDING AGREEMENT TO BIND US TOGETHER SO THAT WE CAN RECEIVE THIS

MONEY INTO A FOREIGN ACCOUNT OR ANY ACCOUNT OF YOUR CHOICE WHERE THE
FUND WILL BE REMITTED.

I AM CONTACTING YOU BECAUSE OF THE NEED TO INVOLVE A FOREIGNER WITH A
FOREIGN ACCOUNT AS THE REAL BENEFICIARY. I NEED YOUR CO-OPERATION TO
MAKE THIS WORK FINE, BECAUSE THE MANAGEMENT IS READY TO APPROVE THIS
PAYMENT TO ANY FOREIGNER WHO HAS THE CORRECT INFORMATION TO THIS ACCOUNT.

WHICH I WILL GIVE TO YOU WHEN SURE OF YOUR CAPABILITY TO HANDLE SUCH
AMOUNT IN STRICT CONFIDENCE AND TRUST, ACCORDING TO MY INSTRUCTIONS AND
MY
ADIVICE FOR OUR MUTUAL BENEFIT BECAUSE I DON'T WANT TO MAKE ANY
MISTAKE, I NEED YOUR STRONG ASSURANCE AND TRUST. I SHALL DESTROYED ALL
DOCUMENT CONCERNING THIS TRANSACTIONS IMMEDIATELY WE RECEIVED THIS MONEY

LEAVING NO TRACE TO ANY PLACE.I WILL USE MY POSITION AND INFLUENCE ON OTHER

STAFFS TO EFFECT THE LEGAL APPROVALS AND ONWARD TRANSFER OF THIS MONEY
TO YOUR ACCOUNT WITH APPROPRIATE CLEARANCE FROM FOREIGN PAYMENT
DEPARTMENT. WITH ASSURANCE THAT
THIS MONEY WILL BE INTACT PENDING MY PHYSICAL ARRIVAL TO YOUR COUNTRY
FOR THE SHARING AND OTHER INVESTMENT.
AT THE CONCLUSION OF THIS BUSINESS, YOU WILL BE GIVEN 30% OF THE TOTAL
AMOUNT, 60% WILL BE FOR ME, WHILE 10% WILL BE FOR EXPENSES , BOTH
PARTIES MIGHT HAVE INCURED DURING THE PROCESS OF THIS TRANSACTION.
I LOOK FORWARD TO YOUR EARLIEST REPLY THROUGH MY PRIVATE E- MAIL
ADDRESS : donaldmbeki001@yahoo.com

YOURS TRULY.

MR DONALD MBEKI








--------------------------
Posílejte SMS pøes internet zdarma a bez reklamy. Pouze s TISCALI.
Více na http://www.tiscali.cz





</p>

</body></html>