<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="MboxParser-x-brightmail-tracker" content="AAAAAA== 21 Jun 2005 07:43:24 -0400 (EDT) my affiliate in Europe and had the funds available in main land Euro=" />
<meta name="subject" content="Think about it..." />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-disposition" content="inline" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="j_a_l_fred@eresmas.com" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/html; charset=us-ascii n with m" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="j_a_l_fred@eresmas.com later that week. This was the last communication we had" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-type" content="text/html; charset=us-ascii" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-disposition" content="inline you and about this project. I repeat, I do not want you contacting m=" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="Think about it..." />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-id" content="&lt;fb457fe022.fe022fb457@ma24.eresmas.com&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Brightmail-Tracker" content="AAAAAA==" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;fb457fe022.fe022fb457@ma24.eresmas.com&gt; rarely held under a name; depositors use numbers and codes to make t=" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="James Jal Alfred &lt;j_a_l_fred@eresmas.com&gt; familiar especially to the highly placed and well-connected organiza=" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="James Jal Alfred &lt;j_a_l_fred@eresmas.com&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2005-06-21T11:37:01Z" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-language" content="en the risks and the only risk I have here is from you refusing to work=" />
<meta name="format" content="text/html; charset=us-ascii n with m" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2005-06-21T11:37:01Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;j_a_l_fred@eresmas.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-mailer" content="Netscape Webmail of the file relating to the customer. I will then officially communi=" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-IronPort-AV" content="i=&quot;3.93,217,1115006400&quot;;    d=&quot;scan'208&quot;; a=&quot;67456286:sNHT25224336&quot; 21 Jun 2005 07:43:25 -0400 (EDT) 21 Jun 2005 07:43:24 -0400 (EDT)" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Tue Jun 21 07:43:42 2005" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-accept-language" content="en" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Reply-to" content="j_a_fred@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="James Jal Alfred" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="James Jal Alfred &lt;j_a_l_fred@eresmas.com&gt; familiar especially to the highly placed and well-connected organiza=" />
<meta name="Author" content="James Jal Alfred &lt;j_a_l_fred@eresmas.com&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Mailer" content="Netscape Webmail" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="James Jal Alfred &lt;j_a_l_fred@eresmas.com&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;fb457fe022.fe022fb457@ma24.eresmas.com&gt; rarely held under a name; depositors use numbers and codes to make t=" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:PMDF-SMTP-Warning" content="Lines longer than SMTP allows found and truncated." />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Accept-Language" content="en" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="James Jal Alfred &lt;j_a_l_fred@eresmas.com&gt; familiar especially to the highly placed and well-connected organiza=" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="James Jal Alfred &lt;j_a_l_fred@eresmas.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-ironport-av" content="i=&quot;3.93,217,1115006400&quot;;  subject matter; ref: bb/tsb/bank/73 came to our bank to engage in bu=" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2005-06-21T11:37:01Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-transfer-encoding" content="QUOTED-PRINTABLE" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="j_a_l_fred@eresmas.com later that week. This was the last communication we had" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="j_a_l_fred@eresmas.com" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-language" content="en" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="MboxParser-reply-to" content="j_a_fred@yahoo.com those wh" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="QUOTED-PRINTABLE with me and alerting my bank. I am the only one who knows of this si=" />
<meta name="creator" content="James Jal Alfred &lt;j_a_l_fred@eresmas.com&gt; familiar especially to the highly placed and well-connected organiza=" />
<meta name="creator" content="James Jal Alfred &lt;j_a_l_fred@eresmas.com&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2 21 Jun 2005 07:43:25 -0400 (EDT) the task he was asking of us. Cash movement across borders has becom=" />
<meta name="MboxParser-dress" content="jamesalfred@i12.com.&amp;nbsp; I do not want any direc" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;j_a_l_fred@eresmas.com&gt; d=&quot;scan'208&quot;; a=&quot;67456286:sNHT25224336&quot; unds to=20" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0 it to yo" />
<meta name="MboxParser-pmdf-smtp-warning" content="Lines longer than SMTP allows found and truncated." />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-1703" />
<title>Think about it...</title>
</head>
<body><table><tr>		<td><p>James Alfred
Lloyds TSB Pacific Limited
Hong Kong Branch</p>


<p> Thank you for giving me your time. Please be patient and read my email to you.
I am a staff of Lloyds TSB Group attached in Private Banking Services. I am contacting you concerning a customer and, an investment placed under our banks management 3 years ago, I contacted you independently of our investigation and no one is informed of this communication and I would like to intimate you with certain facts that I believe would be of interest to you.
 In 2000, the subject matter; ref: bb/tsb/bank/73 came to our bank to engage in business discussions with our Private Banking Services Department. He informed us that he had a financial portfolio of 8.35 million United States Dollars, which he wished to have us turn over on his behalf. I was the officer assigned to his case; I made numerous suggestions in line with my duties as the de-facto chief operations officer of the Private Banking Services Department, especially given the volume of funds he wished to put into our bank. We met on numerous o
 unds to 
cater for banking and statutory charges. He complained about the charges but later came around when I explained to him the complexities of the task he was asking of us. Cash movement across borders has become especially strict since the incidents of 9/11.
 I contacted my affiliate in Europe and had the funds available in main land Europe. I undertook all the processes and made sure I followed his precise instructions to the latter and had the funds deposited in a security consultancy firm, the firm is a specialist private firm that accepts deposits from high net worth individuals and blue chip corporations that handle valuable products or undertake transactions that need immediate access to cash. This small and highly private organization is familiar especially to the highly placed and well-connected organizations. In line with instructions, the money was deposited. He told me he wanted the money there in anticipation of his arrival from Norway later that week. This was the last communication we had
 those wh
o patronize our services usually prefer anonymity, but also some levels of detachment from conventional processes. In his bio-data form, he listed no next of kin. In the field of private banking, opening an account with us means no one will know of its existence, accounts are rarely held under a name; depositors use numbers and codes to make the accounts anonymous. This bank also gives the choice to depositors of having their mail sent to them or held at the bank itself, ensuring that there are no traces of the account and as I said, rarely do they nominate next of kin. Private banking clients apart from not nominating next of kin also usually in most cases leave wills in our care.
 What I wish to relate to you will smack of unethical practice but I want you to understand something. It is only an outsider to the banking world who finds the internal politics of the banking world aberrational. The world of private banking especially is fraught with huge rewards for those who occupy certain offices and
 it to yo
u as the closest surviving relation. Upon receipt of the deposit, I am prepared to share the money with you in half and no more. That is: I will simply nominate you as the next of kin and have them release the deposit to you. We share the proceeds 50/50.I would have gone ahead to ask the funds be released to me, but that would have drawn a straight line to me and my involvement in claiming the deposit. But on the other hand, would easily pass as the beneficiary solo with the rights to claim. I assure you that I could have the deposit released to you in a few days. I will simply inform our bank of the final closing of the file relating to the customer. I will then officially communicate with the finance company and instruct them to release the deposit to you. With these two things: all is done. The alternative would be for us to have the firm direct the funds to another bank with you as account holder. This way there will be no need for you to think of receiving the money from the firm. We can fine-tune this
 n with m
y life but do not destroy me. I am a family man and this is an opportunity to provide them with new opportunities. There is a reward for this project and it is a task well worth undertaking. I have evaluated the risks and the only risk I have here is from you refusing to work with me and alerting my bank. I am the only one who knows of this situation, good fortune has blessed you with a name that has planted you into the center of relevance in my life. Let's share the blessing. If you find yourself able to work with me, contact me through this email account:jamesalfred@i12.com. If you give me positive signals, I will initiate this process towards a conclusion. I wish to inform you that should you contact me via official channels; I will deny knowing you and about this project. I repeat, I do not want you contacting me through my official phone lines nor do I want you contacting me through my official email account. Contact me only through this email address:jamesalfred@i12.com.  I do not want any direc



</p>

</td></tr>

</table>

</body></html>