<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="MboxParser-x-originating-ip" content="[193.220.212.40]" />
<meta name="subject" content="Greetings...From Rabi" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2005-10-08T00:03:52Z" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-originating-server" content="[localhost]" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="Greetings...From Rabi" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Originating-Server" content="[localhost]" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;20051008000352.AFF028DB3E0@server1.eqqu.com&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain;	charset=&quot;iso-8859-1&quot;" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2005-10-08T00:03:52Z" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2 " />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2005-10-08T00:03:52Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;apache@eqqu.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-mailer" content="DWmail 3.6.2" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Fri Oct  7 22:59:23 2005" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;apache@eqqu.com&gt; charset=&quot;iso-8859-1&quot;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-Id" content="&lt;20051008000352.AFF028DB3E0@server1.eqqu.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Originating-IP" content="[193.220.212.40]" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Mailer" content="DWmail 3.6.2" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-1888" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;20051008000352.AFF028DB3E0@server1.eqqu.com&gt;" />
<title>Greetings...From Rabi</title>
</head>
<body><p>
Greetings, 

My name is RABI AL SALIH, wife of MAHAMMED MAHDI AL SALIH,the former 
Iraqi minister for Interior Affairs. I got your email address through the internet while searching for a reliable person to help me and I believe you can be able to help me and my family.
 
My husband was captured on 23 April 2003 by the US forces. My Husband 
is presently in jail and facing trial on charges of terrorism, corruption, embezzlement and the mysterious charge of plunder which might lead to death sentence. During my husband's regime as Minister for Interior, I realized some reasonable amount of money from 
various deals that I successfully executed. I have plans to invest this 
money for my children's future on real estate and industrial production. 
My husband is not aware of this because I wish to do it secretly for now. 

Before the US invaded our nation, I secretly siphoned the sum of 
$12,000,000 million USD out of Iraq and deposited the money with a security firm that transports valuable goods and consignments through diplomatic means. I also declared that the consignment was solid gold belonging to my foreign business partner. I am contacting you 
because I want you to go to the security company and claim the money on my 
behalf since I have declared that the consignment belong to my foreign business partner. You shall also be required to assist me in investment in your country. 

I trust you as a reliable person who will not sit on this money when you claim it, rather assist me properly I expect you to declare what percentage of the total money you will take for your assistance. 
when I receive your positve response I will give you all the necessary 
informations to enable you proceed to the security company and claim the money. I shall also let you know where the security company is and the consignment pin code to claim the consignment, which is very important. I assure you 100% safety and success once you follow my instructions.

For now, let all our communication be by e-mail because my line are tight now connected to the US Forces Telecomunication Network services. Please also send me your telephone and fax number. I will give more details when I receive your reply.

Yours Sincerely,
Rabi.

Eqqu! New Generation email! http://email.eqqu.com


</p>

</body></html>