<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="MboxParser-x-originating-ip" content="196.1.179.58" />
<meta name="subject" content="ASSISTANCE FOR FORIEGN INVESTMENT" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="Mrs Grace &lt;mrs_grace@virgilio.it&gt; After his death I acted fast  and required to" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="Mrs Grace &lt;mrs_grace@virgilio.it&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2005-11-13T19:38:05Z" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="mrs_grace@virgilio.it" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain;charset=&quot;UTF-8&quot;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="MboxParser-reply-to" content="1mrs_grace@myway.com Now I am seeking for a reliable foreigner" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Reply-To" content="1mrs_grace@myway.com" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="ASSISTANCE FOR FORIEGN INVESTMENT" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="7bit" />
<meta name="creator" content="Mrs Grace &lt;mrs_grace@virgilio.it&gt; After his death I acted fast  and required to" />
<meta name="creator" content="Mrs Grace &lt;mrs_grace@virgilio.it&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain;charset=&quot;UTF-8&quot;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="Mrs Grace &lt;mrs_grace@virgilio.it&gt; After his death I acted fast  and required to" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="Mrs Grace &lt;mrs_grace@virgilio.it&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2005-11-13T19:38:05Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Mime-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain;charset=&quot;UTF-8&quot;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2 I was moved by my personal inspiration to entrust on your" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2005-11-13T19:38:05Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="7bit" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;mrs_grace@virgilio.it&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Sun Nov 13 14:43:57 2005" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;mrs_grace@virgilio.it&gt; I am making this contact to you" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="Mrs Grace" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="Mrs Grace &lt;mrs_grace@virgilio.it&gt; After his death I acted fast  and required to" />
<meta name="Author" content="Mrs Grace &lt;mrs_grace@virgilio.it&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Originating-IP" content="196.1.179.58" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-1953" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="Mrs Grace &lt;mrs_grace@virgilio.it&gt;" />
<title>ASSISTANCE FOR FORIEGN INVESTMENT</title>
</head>
<body><p>FROM; MRS GRACE BOLA IGE


Greetings,
  I am making this contact to you 
on the fact that we may be of assistance to each other in developing a 
long lasting cordial business relationship, if you put your trust in  
God that this will work out forthe benefit of my own family and 
yours.  

  I was moved by my personal inspiration to entrust on your 
sincerity to  handle a business relationship that involves huge money 
on trust. I was  constrained by the sudden death of my husband, the 
former Minister of  Power andsteel and currently before his death, the 
Minister for Justice  of my country, whom was assassinated by an 
unknown men.
 I am Mrs. grace Bola Ige, the second wife of the late Mr. 
Bola Ige who died on  December 23rd 2001. With heart full of grief, I 
regret to inform you of  the inhumane and harsh conditions which my 
husband's first wife and the brother's have subjected my two daughters 
and me. Since my husband's death,the relatives have been wicked to us 
because of the following reasons:

1. I am not from the same tribe with 
them,

2. My refusal to  learn and speak their tribal language and 
dress like other women from their tribe,
3. My refusal to accept their 
religion,

4. Because I have  no male child,

5. Because I was 
specially loved and favored I am  absolutely tired of all these threats 
from my husband relatives since the death of my husband.

I am no 
longer in their Family house. am now  in my husband's guesthouse, with 
my daughters, I seriously need your kind assistance and co-operations.
Few weeks before my husband's death, he entrusted some security 
documents that cover a deposit he made to a security company to the 
tune of 25 million U.S dollars to my care for  safe keeping in my 
apartment in Abuja.

 After his death I acted fast  and required to 
gather information about the consignment. I was made to know that it 
was deposited as family treasure of a foreigner/associate  to be 
delivered on request. This fund was deposited for safe keeping with a 
Private Security Company.

 Now I am seeking for a reliable foreigner 
who can come down to clear the funds in his/her name as the  sole 
beneficiary of the Consignment. This is so because of my status here as 
a widow of a political juggernaut. Now I solicit your assistance to 
accept this sum for self-keeping. This I cannot lodge into a bank 
account here in my name to avoid suspicion from the Government, my 
husband's brother's and wife since they have Confiscated all that is 
left by my husband and still places eyes on me if they could lay hands 
on more including cash as they have left me and my  children without 
any cash.
If you can accept this, I urge you to  contact us immediately 
for us to brief you on arrangement on how we can  possibly handle this.

This is why I honestly contacted you because investing this money 
abroad should be the best for my dauthers and me. I will be honored if 
I can be given the privilege of dealing with the investment proceeding 
with you.

I expect you to be trustworthy and kind enough to respond to 
this distress call to save US from a hopeless future. And if you agree, 
I hereby agree to compensate your sincere and candid effort in this 
regard with 30% of the principal sum. While the remaining 70% will be 
invested meaningfully for our future if possible in your area of 
business and different sectors of the Economy in your  country which 
are dividends yielding. Whatever your decision is please  reach me 
immediately through my email.And keep this letter tight secret  for the 
interest of my Family.

I regret to inform you of the inhumane  and 
harsh conditions which my husband's first wife Justice Mrs. Atinuke Ige 
and the brother's have subjected me and my two daughters. Since my  
husband death, the relatives have been wicked to us in my husband 
family.

I hope to hear from you soon.

MRS GRACE BOLA IGE





</p>

</body></html>