<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sender" content="ojeiuloaku05@hotmail.com" />
<meta name="subject" content="Charity Funds / Trustee Needed" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="&quot;Dr. Ojei Uloaku&quot; &lt;ojeiuloaku05@hotmail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="Dr. Ojei Uloaku &lt;ojeiuloaku05@hotmail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="O" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="ojeiuloaku05@hotmail.com" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2005-12-24T13:47:08Z" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; format=flowed" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="O" />
<meta name="MboxParser-reply-to" content="ojeiuloaku1@yahoo.es" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Reply-To" content="ojeiuloaku1@yahoo.es" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="Charity Funds / Trustee Needed" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-OriginalArrivalTime" content="24 Dec 2005 13:47:08.0886 (UTC) FILETIME=[88BA4760:01C60890]" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Originating-Email" content="[ojeiuloaku05@hotmail.com]" />
<meta name="creator" content="&quot;Dr. Ojei Uloaku&quot; &lt;ojeiuloaku05@hotmail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="Dr. Ojei Uloaku &lt;ojeiuloaku05@hotmail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; format=flowed" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="&quot;Dr. Ojei Uloaku&quot; &lt;ojeiuloaku05@hotmail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="Dr. Ojei Uloaku &lt;ojeiuloaku05@hotmail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2005-12-24T13:47:08Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Mime-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; format=flowed" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2005-12-24T13:47:08Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;ojeiuloaku05@hotmail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="Message-Bcc" content="" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-originalarrivaltime" content="24 Dec 2005 13:47:08.0886 (UTC) FILETIME=[88BA4760:01C60890]" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sender" content="ojeiuloaku05@hotmail.com" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Sat Dec 24 08:47:16 2005" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-originating-email" content="[ojeiuloaku05@hotmail.com]" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;ojeiuloaku05@hotmail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="Dr. Ojei Uloaku" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="&quot;Dr. Ojei Uloaku&quot; &lt;ojeiuloaku05@hotmail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="Author" content="Dr. Ojei Uloaku &lt;ojeiuloaku05@hotmail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-2041" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="Dr. Ojei Uloaku &lt;ojeiuloaku05@hotmail.com&gt;" />
<title>Charity Funds / Trustee Needed</title>
</head>
<body><p>Dear Trustee,

As you read this, I don't want you feeling sorry for
me, because, I believe we will all die someday.My name
is DR. OJEI ULOAKU, an oil Merchant living in Nigeria,
West Africa. I have been diagnosed with Esophageal
Cancer,which was discovered very late, due to my
laxity in caring for my health. It has defied all
forms of medicine, and right now I have only about a
few months to live, according to medical experts.
I have not particularly lived my life so well, as I
never really cared for anyone not even myself but my
business. Though I am very rich, I was never generous,
I fought against the abolition of apartheid and l was
a member of the leading party in Nigeria always
hostile to people especially my fellow Blacks and l
only focused on my business and the dominance of the
white supremacy as that was the only thing I cared
for. But now I regret all these,as I now know that
there is more to life than just wanting to have or
make all the money in the world. I believe
reincarnation when l have a second chance to come to
this world I would live my life a different way from
how I have lived it.

So far, I have distributed money to some charity
organizations e.g. the National Union of Ivory Coast
Students (NUIVS) in Ivory Coast, Romania and
Afghanistan. Now that my health has deteriorated so
badly, I cannot do this my self anymore. I once asked
members of my family to close one of my accounts and
distribute the money, which I have there to charity
organization and to the less privileged in Bulgaria
and Pakistan, they refused and kept the money to
themselves. Hence, I do not trust them anymore, as
they seem not to be contended with what I have left
for them, and have not learn the lesson of all been
equal in the sight of God Almighty.

The last of my money, which l had kept aside during
the dark days of political blood shed in Africa no one
knows of, is a cash deposit of Eighty Four Million
United States Dollars (US$84,000,000.00) that I have
with a bank in Nigeria for safekeeping. I will want
you to help me collect this deposit and disburse it to
charity organizations and to the less privileged,based
on the reason l kept the money, was to do evil, l want
it now to be used for the good of all mankind.Please
send me a mail to indicate if you will assist me in
this disbursement.
God will reward you for your time and patience.
I wait to hear from you, may Almighty God be with you
and your entire family.
Yours in the Lord.  Call me at +234 803 384 8734.

Best regards

Dr. Ojei Uloaku.

This transmission contains information which may be confidential and which 
may also be privileged.  It is intended for the named addressee only.  
Unless you are the named addressee, or authorised to receive it on behalf of 
the addressee you may not copy or use it, or disclose it to anyone else.  If 
you have received this transmission in error please contact the sender.  
Thank you for your cooperation.




</p>

</body></html>