<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Spam-Status" content="Yes, score=10.9 required=5.0 tests=ADVANCE_FEE_1,ADVANCE_FEE_2,	ADVANCE_FEE_3,BAYES_20,DATE_IN_PAST_06_12,MILLION_USD,SUBJ_ALL_CAPS,	TO_CC_NONE,TO_EMPTY,X_PRIORITY_CC autolearn=no version=3.1.0" />
<meta name="subject" content="GOD BLESS YOU FROM MRS. ELENA OWEN" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="&quot;MRS.ELENA OWEN&quot; &lt;elenaowen@sify.com&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="MRS.ELENA OWEN &lt;elenaowen@sify.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-name" content="Barr. Joseph Alford Esq." />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-spam-flag" content="YES" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="O" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="elenaowen@sify.com" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=us-ascii" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="newman.eecs.UM" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="O" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-spam-status" content="Yes, score=10.9 required=5.0 tests=ADVANCE_FEE_1,ADVANCE_FEE_2," />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Spam-Checker-Version" content="SpamAssassin 3.1.0 (2005-09-13) on 	newman.eecs.UM" />
<meta name="MboxParser-email" content="josephalford@o2.pl" />
<meta name="MboxParser-email" content="alfordjoseph@satellite-email.com" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="GOD BLESS YOU FROM MRS. ELENA OWEN" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Spam-Flag" content="YES" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-virus-scan" content=": UVSCAN at UoM/EECS" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Spam-Level" content="**********" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="7bit" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-spam-level" content="**********" />
<meta name="creator" content="&quot;MRS.ELENA OWEN&quot; &lt;elenaowen@sify.com&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="MRS.ELENA OWEN &lt;elenaowen@sify.com&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; charset=us-ascii" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="&quot;MRS.ELENA OWEN&quot; &lt;elenaowen@sify.com&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="MRS.ELENA OWEN &lt;elenaowen@sify.com&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Mime-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=us-ascii" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2 TO_CC_NONE,TO_EMPTY,X_PRIORITY_CC autolearn=no version=3.1.0" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="7bit" />
<meta name="Message-Cc" content="" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;root@mphotostudio.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-mailer" content="RLSP Mailer" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-priority" content="3 (Normal)" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Priority" content="3 (Normal)" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-spam-checker-version" content="SpamAssassin 3.1.0 (2005-09-13) on " />
<meta name="MboxParser-tel/fax" content="44-70-40109983" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Fri Jan 13 16:57:51 2006" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;root@mphotostudio.com&gt; ADVANCE_FEE_3,BAYES_20,DATE_IN_PAST_06_12,MILLION_USD,SUBJ_ALL_CAPS," />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="MRS.ELENA OWEN" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Virus-Scan" content=": UVSCAN at UoM/EECS" />
<meta name="Author" content="&quot;MRS.ELENA OWEN&quot; &lt;elenaowen@sify.com&gt;" />
<meta name="Author" content="MRS.ELENA OWEN &lt;elenaowen@sify.com&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Mailer" content="RLSP Mailer" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-2080" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="MRS.ELENA OWEN &lt;elenaowen@sify.com&gt;" />
<title>GOD BLESS YOU FROM MRS. ELENA OWEN</title>
</head>
<body><p>
&gt;From Mrs. Elena Owen

London, W8 5DL,

4 Kensington Court,

England.



I am Mrs. Elena Owen, a citizen of Bulgaria but I based in England, I am married to Sir Francis Owen who also is an Englishman though dead now. My husband worked with the British Railways for over two decade before the cold hand of death took him away on the 3rd of June 2005 at about 2:00AM our marriage lasted for over a decade without any fruit of the womb.



My husband died after a protracted illness. My husband and I made a vow to uplift the down-trodden and the less-privileged individuals within the Europe, North and South America, Africa and the rest of the Globe as he had passion for persons who cannot help hemselves due to physical disability or financial predicament. I can adduce this to the fact that he needed a Child from this relationship, which never came.



When my late husband was alive he deposited the sum of $10.5 Million (Ten Million Five Hundred Thousand United State Dollars in a dormant Account in one of the leading security and Finance company in Europe. this money is still with the Finance Company. Presently, am suffering from cancerous ailment for some years now. Recently, my Doctor told me that I have a limited or numbered days on earth and that my life Spam will not exceed 150days due to the cancerous problems I am suffering from.



Though what bothers me most is the stroke that I have in addition to the cancer. With this hard reality that has befallen my family, I have decided to donate this fund to a non-governmental, or better still an individual, that will utilize this money the way I am going to instruct here in., that will use this gift which comes from my husbands sweat to fund the upkeep of widows, orphans, destitute, the down-trodden, physically challenged children, barren-women and persons who prove to be genuinely handicapped financially. It is often said that blessed is the hand that gives.



I took this decision because I do not have any child that will inherit this money and my husband relatives are Bourgeois and very wealthy persons and I do not want my husband hard earned money to be misused by his relatives whom have already sold all his landed property. I do not want a situation where this money will be used in an ungodly manner, hence the reason for taking this bold decision. I am not afraid of death hence I know where I am going.



I know that I am going to be with the Almighty when I eventually pass on.The Almighty will fight my case and I shall hold my peace. I do not need any telephone communication in this regard due to my deteriorating health and because of the presence of my husband relatives around me. I do not want them to know about this development. With God all things are possible. 



I will want you to contact my personal attorney base in Manchester (U.K) on the information stated below, whom I have entrusted every detail regarding this fund.



Name: Barr. Joseph Alford Esq.

Tel/Fax: 44-70-40109983

Email: josephalford@o2.pl

Email: alfordjoseph@satellite-email.com



Required information.



1) Your full name and address

2) Your private phone, mobile and fax number where you can always be reach. 





As Soon as your information is been received by my attorney, he will also issue a Letter of Authority and power of attorney on this regard, making you the original beneficiary of this fund with other related documents. My happiness is that I lived a life worthy of emulation. Please always be prayerfully all through your life.



Any delay in your reply will give me room in sourcing for a non-governmental, a non-religious, and or a non-profit organization better still an individual for this same purpose. Please assure me that you will act just as I have stated herein. Hope to hear from you soon and God bless you and members of your family.



Mrs. Elena Owen. Benefactor 







___________________________________________________________________________
Mail sent from WebMail service at PHP-Nuke Powered Site

- http://yoursite.com


</p>

</body></html>