<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="Ken Quattara." />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="&quot;Mr.Ken Quattara.&quot; &lt;ken211@o2.pl&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="Mr.Ken Quattara. &lt;ken211@o2.pl&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="O" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="ken211@o2.pl" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2006-01-16T23:39:23Z" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="sigmod-pods06-webmaster@UM" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="sigmod-pods06-webmaster@UM" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;us-ascii&quot;" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="sigmod-pods06-webmaster@UM" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="O" />
<meta name="MboxParser-reply-to" content="ken211@o2.pl" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Reply-To" content="ken211@o2.pl" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="Ken Quattara." />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;200601162336.k0GNaPbl030920@jacknife.mail.UM&gt; " />
<meta name="creator" content="&quot;Mr.Ken Quattara.&quot; &lt;ken211@o2.pl&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="Mr.Ken Quattara. &lt;ken211@o2.pl&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;us-ascii&quot;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="&quot;Mr.Ken Quattara.&quot; &lt;ken211@o2.pl&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="Mr.Ken Quattara. &lt;ken211@o2.pl&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2006-01-16T23:39:23Z" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;us-ascii&quot;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2 Or you may choose to arrange something else with the agent=28s=29=2E If" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2006-01-16T23:39:23Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;sigmod-pods06-webmaster-errors@UM&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-mailer" content="Microsoft Outlook Express 5.00.2919.6900 DM" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Mon Jan 16 18:36:32 2006" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;sigmod-pods06-webmaster-errors@UM&gt; " />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-Id" content="&lt;200601162336.k0GNaPbl030920@jacknife.mail.UM&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="Mr.Ken Quattara." />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="&quot;Mr.Ken Quattara.&quot; &lt;ken211@o2.pl&gt;" />
<meta name="Author" content="Mr.Ken Quattara. &lt;ken211@o2.pl&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Mailer" content="Microsoft Outlook Express 5.00.2919.6900 DM" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-2091" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="Mr.Ken Quattara. &lt;ken211@o2.pl&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;200601162336.k0GNaPbl030920@jacknife.mail.UM&gt; " />
<title>Ken Quattara.</title>
</head>
<body><p>
Mr.Ken Quattara.
Ghana.

Good day to you!
I am requesting for your assistance in a deal of Considerable
financial gain for both of us.
I am Ken Quattara, I was the Personal Assistant (P.A) to the former
President of The Federal Republic of Togo, the late President
Gnassingbe Eyadema.
In the last week of January 2005, two security deposit boxes were
deposited on behalf of Mr. Eyadema by me with a company in Ghana.
The boxes contained 35 million dollars in cash. I have the
certificate of deposit issued by the company for the boxes. As his
trusted P.A I had employed the services of this particular company
to arrange the shipment of the boxes to Europe on his behalf were
they were to be picked up by a foreign associate of his at that
time, a French man.
This was not the first time I had arranged this kind of shipment for
Mr.Eyadema using this company. The boxes were labeled "photographic
materials" to elude customs and other checks.
Unfortunately, because he was ill-disposed at the time the French
man was no longer able to make the trip to meet with the company's
agents at the destination point. So the agents who accompanied the
boxes had to deposit them in a storage facility pending when he
could come.
On the 5th of February 2005, Mr Eyadema passed on while he was being
evacuated abroad for emergency medical treatment. He had been ill
for some years.
Following the demise of my former Boss, his associate withdrew, so
the boxes have been in storage since then. It was my function to
issue his associates Letters Of Athorization signed by me to pick up
boxes containing valuables and money. They banked money for him in
various pre-selected banks in Europe and Asia. The agents only
assisted the associates in the process to ensure that everything was
done under diplomatic immunity and within the stipulated laws in the
countries where such transactions took place.
I am asking for your assistance and involvement so that we can get
the money for ourselves. I can not do this on my own because i can't
so to say, authorize myself. If you accept to act as an associate of
the Late Mr Eyadema, I can issue to you the Letter of Authorization
for the purpose of reclaiming the boxes on his behalf for our own
benefit. As the beneficiary it will be your responsibility and
obligation (as stated in the coded agreement between the depositor
and the company) to reclaim and repossess the boxes from the storage
facility.
You will be required to meet with the company's assigned agent(s)
personally.
This way you will see the boxes for yourself and sign the necessary
documents to reposses the boxes. The agent(s) will assist you to
bank the funds and then thereafter you can transfer money to other
offshore accounts. This was how itwas done with previous associates.
 Or you may choose to arrange something else with the agent(s). If
however you can not meet with any assigned agent, as the
beneficiary/associate to the Late Eyadema,you could request that an
alternative arrangement be made for you. You will have to discuss
this with the agent(s) yourself.
I assure you that everything will go smoothly if you choose to
cooperate with the agent(s). There is no illegality involved here.
If you do decide to get involved then i expect total commitment from
you. If you can do this, i am offering you 3 million dollars as your
own share.
If you are interested in this deal, then contact me immediately via
email(furnished above) for further details. Thank you for your time.

Regards,
Ken Quattara





</p>

</body></html>