<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="From Mr.John Mmadu" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="&quot;Mr.John&quot; &lt;john2mmadu@ozu.es&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="Mr.John &lt;john2mmadu@ozu.es&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2006-01-20T01:12:11Z" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="john2mmadu@ozu.es" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain;charset=iso-8859-1" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="undisclosed-recipients:;" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="undisclosed-recipients:;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Importance" content="Normal" />
<meta name="MboxParser-reply-to" content="johnmmadu1@latinmail.com" />
<meta name="MboxParser-user-agent" content="SquirrelMail/1.4.2" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-ID" content="&lt;35651.80.179.250.148.1137719531.squirrel@correo.ozu.es&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="From Mr.John Mmadu" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Reply-To" content="johnmmadu1@latinmail.com" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:User-Agent" content="SquirrelMail/1.4.2" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2        Fri, 20 Jan 2006 02:12:11 +0100 (CET)" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;35651.80.179.250.148.1137719531.squirrel@correo.ozu.es&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="&quot;Mr.John&quot; &lt;john2mmadu@ozu.es&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="Mr.John &lt;john2mmadu@ozu.es&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain;charset=iso-8859-1" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="&quot;Mr.John&quot; &lt;john2mmadu@ozu.es&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="Mr.John &lt;john2mmadu@ozu.es&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2006-01-20T01:12:11Z" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain;charset=iso-8859-1" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2 {Very Urgent Business Transaction}" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2006-01-20T01:12:11Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;john2mmadu@ozu.es&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-priority" content="3" />
<meta name="MboxParser-attention" content="" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Priority" content="3" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Thu Jan 19 20:12:28 2006" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;john2mmadu@ozu.es&gt; Fri, 20 Jan 2006 02:12:11 +0100 (CET)" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="Mr.John" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="&quot;Mr.John&quot; &lt;john2mmadu@ozu.es&gt;" />
<meta name="Author" content="Mr.John &lt;john2mmadu@ozu.es&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-importance" content="Normal" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-2103" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="Mr.John &lt;john2mmadu@ozu.es&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;35651.80.179.250.148.1137719531.squirrel@correo.ozu.es&gt;" />
<title>From Mr.John Mmadu</title>
</head>
<body><p>&gt;From Mr.John Mmadu
Auditing and accounting unit.
Foreign remittance dept.
United bank for africa plc.
Abuja-Nigeria.

Attention:

                    {Very Urgent Business Transaction}


Greetings

In order to transfer out (usd 32 million dollars) from
our bank. i have the courage to ask you to look for a
reliable and honest person who will be capable for
this important business believing that you will never
let me down either now or in future.

I am Mr.John Mmadu ,the auditor general of United Bank
for Africa plc.(uba).there is an account opened in
this bank in 1980 and since 1990 nobody has operated
on this account again. after going through some old
files in the records i discovered that if i do not
remitt this money out urgently it will be forfeited
for nothing.

The owner of this account is Mr. Carlos .M.Brown a
foreigner, and the manager of petro - technical
support services, a chemical engineer by profession
and he died since 1990. no other person knows about
this account or any thing concerning it, the account
has no other beneficiary and my investigation proved
to me as well that this companydoes not know anything
about this account and the amount involved is (USD
32million Dollars).

I want to transfer this money into a safe foreigners
account abroad but i don't know any foreigner, i am
only contacting you as a foreigner because this money
can not be approved to a local bank here,but can only
be approved to any foreign account because the money
is in US dollars and the former owner of the account
is Mr. Carlos .M.Brown is a foreigner too. I know that
this message will come to you as a surprise as we
don't know our selves before but be sure that it is
real and a genuine business.

I believe in GOD that you will never let me down in
this business you are the only person that i have
contacted in this business, so please reply urgently
so that i will inform you the next step to take
urgently.

I want us to see face to face or sign a binding
agreement to bind us together so that you can recieve
this money into a foriegn account or any account of
your choice where the fund will be remmitted.and i
will fly to your country for withdrawal and sharing
and other investments.

I am contacting you because of the need to involve a
foreigner with foreign account and foreign
beneficiary. i need your co-operation to make this
work fine. because the management is ready to approve
this payment to any foreigner who has correct
information of this account, which i will give to you
later immediately, if you are able and with capability
to handle such amount in strict confidence and trust
according to my instructions and advice for our mutual
benefit because this opportunity will never come again
in my life. a need truthful person in this business
because i don't want to make mistake i need your
strong assurance and trust.

With my position now in the office i can transfer this
money to any foreigners reliable account which you can
provide with assurance that this money will be intact
pending my physical arrival in your country for
sharing. i will destroy all documents of transaction
immediately we recieve this money leaving no trace to
any place. you can also come to discuss with me face
to face after which i will make this remittance in
your presence and two of us will fly to your country
at least two days ahead of the money going into your
account. i will apply for annual leave to get visa
immediately i hear from you that you are ready to act
and receive this fund in your account. i will use my
position and influence to effect legal approvals and
onward transfer of this money to your account with
appropriate clearance forms of the ministries and
foreign exchange departments. at the conclusion of
this business, you will be given 40% of the total
amount, 60% will be for me, i look forward to your
earliest reply by email.

yours truly

Mr.John Mmadu
Auditor General
United Bank for Africa
Abuja.


--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Nueva Barra de Herramientas de OZÚ. Navega Más facilmente por Internet.
¡Descargatela gratis! http://barra.ozu.es/
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Correo enviado desde http://www.ozu.es


</p>

</body></html>