<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="Can  You  Assist?" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="&quot;Dr.Tito Sithole.&quot; &lt;macusgee@hotmail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="Dr.Tito Sithole. &lt;macusgee@hotmail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="macusgee@hotmail.com" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2003-05-18T20:14:37Z" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="R@M" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="R@M" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;windows-1252&quot;" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="R@M" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="MboxParser-reply-to" content="titosithole@yahoo.ca" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Reply-To" content="titosithole@yahoo.ca" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="Can  You  Assist?" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;200305182016.h4IKG1c16977@truecrime.mr.itd.UM&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="&quot;Dr.Tito Sithole.&quot; &lt;macusgee@hotmail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="Dr.Tito Sithole. &lt;macusgee@hotmail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;windows-1252&quot;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="&quot;Dr.Tito Sithole.&quot; &lt;macusgee@hotmail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="Dr.Tito Sithole. &lt;macusgee@hotmail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2003-05-18T20:14:37Z" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;windows-1252&quot;" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2003-05-18T20:14:37Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;macusgee@hotmail.com&gt;	by truecrime.mr.itd.UM (3.6u) with SMTP id h4IKG1c16977; Sun, 18 May 2003 16:16:05 -0400 (EDT)" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-mailer" content="Microsoft Outlook Express 5.00.2919.6900 DM" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Sun May 18 16:16:45 2003" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;macusgee@hotmail.com&gt; by truecrime.mr.itd.UM (3.6u) with SMTP id h4IKG1c16977; Sun, 18 May 2003 16:16:05 -0400 (EDT)" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-Id" content="&lt;200305182016.h4IKG1c16977@truecrime.mr.itd.UM&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="Dr.Tito Sithole." />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="&quot;Dr.Tito Sithole.&quot; &lt;macusgee@hotmail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="Author" content="Dr.Tito Sithole. &lt;macusgee@hotmail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Mailer" content="Microsoft Outlook Express 5.00.2919.6900 DM" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-226" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="Dr.Tito Sithole. &lt;macusgee@hotmail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;200305182016.h4IKG1c16977@truecrime.mr.itd.UM&gt;" />
<title>Can  You  Assist?</title>
</head>
<body><p>Corporate Line: +27-83-9835788
Confidential Line: + 873 - 762 - 534365
Confidential Fax: +  873 - 762 - 534366


I am Dr.Tito Sithole,  Director of Project Implementation South Africa Department
of Mining &amp; Natural Resources. First and foremost, I apologized using this medium to reach
you for a transaction/business of this magnitude, but this is due to confidentiality
and prompt access reposed on this medium.  I have decided to seek a confidential
co-operation with you in the execution of the deal described hereunder
for the benefit of all parties and hope you will keep it as a top secret because
of the nature of this transaction.

Within the Department of Mining &amp; Natural Resources where I work as
an Executive Accountant and with the cooperation of four other top officials,
we have in our possession as overdue payment bills totaling Twenty-Eight
Million, Five Hundred Thousand U. S. Dollars (US$28,500,000.00) which we want to transfer abroad with the assistance and cooperation of a foreign company/individual to receive the said fund on our behalf or a reliable foreign non-company account to receive such funds. More so, we are handicapped in the circumstances, as the South Africa Civil Service Code of Conduct does not allow us to operate offshore account hence your importance in the whole transaction.

This amount (US$28.5m) represents the balance of the total contract value
executed on behalf of my Department by a foreign contracting firm, which
we the officials over-invoiced deliberately. Though the actual contract cost
have been paid to the original contractor, leaving the balance in the tune
of the said amount which we have in principles gotten approval to remit by Telegraphic Transfer (T.T) to any foreign bank account you will provide by filing in an application through the Justice Ministry here in South Africa for the transfer of rights and privileges of the former contractor to you.

I have the authority of my partners involved to propose that should you
be willing to assist us in the transaction, your share of the sum will be 25%
of the US$28.5 million, 70% for us and 5% for taxation and miscellaneous
expenses. The business itself is 100% safe, on your part provided you treat
it with utmost secrecy and confidentiality. Also your area of specialization
is not a hindrance to the successful execution of this transaction.

I have reposed my confidence in you and hope that you will not disappoint
me. Endeavor to contact me immediately via my confidential fax  whether or
not you are interested in this deal. If you are not, it will enable me contact another
Foreign partner with recommendation to carry out this deal.

I want to assure you that myself and my partners are in a position to make
the payment of this claim possible provided you can give us a very strong
assurance and guarantee that our share will be secured and Please remember
to treat this matter as very confidential matter; because we will not comprehend
with any form of exposure as we are still in active Government Service and
remember once again that time is of the essence in this business .

I wait in anticipation of your fullest co-operation .

Yours faithfully,

Dr.Tito Sithole.



</p>

</body></html>