<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content=" FROM JESSICA PRINCE" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="jessicaprince555@sify.com" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="jessicaprince555@sify.com" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="jessicaprince555@sify.com" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/html" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="aiweb06@cs.umbc.edu &lt;br&gt;EFFORT INPUT AFTER THE SUCCESSFUL TRANSFER OF THIS FUND TO YOUR&lt;br" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="aiweb06@cs.umbc.edu" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="aiweb06@cs.umbc.edu &lt;br&gt;EFFORT INPUT AFTER THE SUCCESSFUL TRANSFER OF THIS FUND TO YOUR&lt;br" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Multipart-Boundary" content="-MOQ1144346298e8adbbf420c9ea119c8d05fad0638728" />
<meta name="dc:title" content=" FROM JESSICA PRINCE" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2	for &lt;aiweb06@cs.umbc.edu&gt;; Thu, 6 Apr 2006 13:34:07 -0400 (EDT)" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="8bit" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="8bit" />
<meta name="creator" content="jessicaprince555@sify.com" />
<meta name="creator" content="jessicaprince555@sify.com" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="jessicaprince555@sify.com" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="jessicaprince555@sify.com" />
<meta name="format" content="text/html" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2 b=jgs+A1eqFKuJmD/KjNuKVm/9v5DwjlhwEKMrOlTKyDxQCRyBNEZlVO8MderFwoGg  ; DJAN. HE SECRETLY CALLED ME ON HIS BEDSIDE&lt;br&gt;AND TOLD ME THAT HE HAS A SUM OF US$18.500.000 (EGHTEEN MILLION&lt;br&gt;FIVEHUNDRED THOUSAND, UNITED STATES DOLLARS) LEFT IN A LOCAL BANK HERE&lt;br&gt;IN ABIDJAN. THAT HE USED MY NAME AS HIS ONLY CHILD FOR THE NEXT OF KIN&lt;br&gt;IN  DEPOSIT OF THE FUND. HE ALSO EXPLAINED TO ME THAT IT WAS BECAUSE OF&lt;br&gt;THIS WEALTH THAT HE WAS POISONED BY HIS BUSINESS ASSOCIATES, THAT I&lt;br&gt;SHOULD SEEK FOR A FOREIGN PARTNER IN A COUNTRY OF MY CHOICE WHERE I WILL&lt;br&gt;TRANSFER THIS MONEY AND USE IT FOR INVESTMENT PURPOSE. (SUCH AS REAL&lt;br&gt;ESTATE MANAGEMENT). I AM HONOURABLY SEEKING YOUR ASSISTANCE IN THE&lt;br&gt;FOLLOWING WAYS : TO PROVIDE A BANK ACCOUNT WHERE THIS MONEY WOULD  BE&lt;br&gt;TRANSFERED TO SERVE AS THE GUARDIAN OF THIS FUND SINCE I AM A GIRL OF 21&lt;br&gt;YEARS TO MAKE ARRANGEMENT FOR ME TO COME OVER TO YOUR COUNTRY TO FURTHER&lt;br&gt;MY EDUCATIONAND TO SECURE A RESIDENTIAL PERMIT IN YOUR COUNTRY. I AM&lt;br&gt;WILLING TO OFFER YOU 30% OF THE TOTAL SUM AS COMPENSATION FOR YOUR!" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;jessicaprince555@sify.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Thu Apr  6 13:34:27 2006" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;jessicaprince555@sify.com&gt; for &lt;aiweb06@cs.umbc.edu&gt;; Thu, 6 Apr 2006 13:34:07 -0400 (EDT) AND TOLD ME THAT HE HAS A SUM OF US$18.500.000 (EGHTEEN MILLION FIVEHUNDRED THOUSAND, UNITED STATES DOLLARS) LEFT IN A LOCAL BANK HERE IN ABIDJAN. THAT HE USED MY NAME AS HIS ONLY CHILD FOR THE NEXT OF KIN IN  DEPOSIT OF THE FUND. HE ALSO EXPLAINED TO ME THAT IT WAS BECAUSE OF THIS WEALTH THAT HE WAS POISONED BY HIS BUSINESS ASSOCIATES, THAT I SHOULD SEEK FOR A FOREIGN PARTNER IN A COUNTRY OF MY CHOICE WHERE I WILL TRANSFER THIS MONEY AND USE IT FOR INVESTMENT PURPOSE. (SUCH AS REAL ESTATE MANAGEMENT). I AM HONOURABLY SEEKING YOUR ASSISTANCE IN THE FOLLOWING WAYS : TO PROVIDE A BANK ACCOUNT WHERE THIS MONEY WOULD  BE TRANSFERED TO SERVE AS THE GUARDIAN OF THIS FUND SINCE I AM A GIRL OF 21 YEARS TO MAKE ARRANGEMENT FOR ME TO COME OVER TO YOUR COUNTRY TO FURTHER MY EDUCATIONAND TO SECURE A RESIDENTIAL PERMIT IN YOUR COUNTRY. I AM WILLING TO OFFER YOU 30% OF THE TOTAL SUM AS COMPENSATION FOR YOUR EFFORT INPUT AFTER THE SUCCESSFUL TRANSFER OF THIS FUND TO YOUR NOMINATED ACCOUN!" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-QHPSI" content="clean  b=jgs+A1eqFKuJmD/KjNuKVm/9v5DwjlhwEKMrOlTKyDxQCRyBNEZlVO8MderFwoGg  ;" />
<meta name="Author" content="jessicaprince555@sify.com" />
<meta name="Author" content="jessicaprince555@sify.com" />
<meta name="Multipart-Subtype" content="alternative" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-2410" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="jessicaprince555@sify.com" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-qhpsi" content="clean T OVERSEAS . FURTHERMORE, YOU CAN INDICATE YOUR OPTION TOWARDS ASSISTI" />
<title> FROM JESSICA PRINCE</title>
</head>
<body><pre>FROM JESSICA PRINCE

COTE D IVOIRE

WEST AFRICA

DEAR FRIEND,

PERMIT ME
TO INFORM YOU OF MY DESIRE OF ENTERING INTO BUSINESS RELATIONSHIP WITH
YOU. I GOT YOUR EMAIL HROUGH A FRIEND  WHO WORKS IN THE HUMAN RIGHTS
COMMISSION HERE IN ABIDJAN COTE D IVOIRE I PRAYED OVER IT AND SELECTED
YOUR NAME AMOUNG OTHER NAMES DUE TO IT'S ESTEEMING NATUREAND THE  
ECOMMENDATIONS GIVEN TO ME AS A REPUTABLE AND TRUSTWORTHY PERSON I CAN
DO BUSINESS WITH AND BY THEIR RECOMMENDATIONS I MUST NOT HESITATE TO
CONFIDE IN YOU FOR THIS SIMPLE AND SINCERE BUSINESS. I AM JESSICA PRINCE
TONY THE ONLY CHILD OF LATE MR AND MRS PRINCE TONY MY FAHTER WAS A VERY
WEALTHY COCOA MERCHANT BASED  IN ABIDJAN. THE ECONOMIC CAPITAL OF IVORY
COAST BEFORE HE WAS POISONED TO DEATH BY HIS BUSINESS ASSOCIATES ON ONE
OF THEIR OUTING TO DISCUSS ON A BUSINESS DEAL. WHEN MY MOTHER DIED ON
THE 21ST OCTOBER 1998. MY FATHER TOOK ME SO SPECIAL BECAUSE I AM
MOTHERLESS. BEFORE THE DEATH OF MY FATHER ON 29TH AUGUST 2000 IN A
PRIVATE HOSPITAL HERE IN ABI!
 DJAN. HE SECRETLY CALLED ME ON HIS BEDSIDE
AND TOLD ME THAT HE HAS A SUM OF US$18.500.000 (EGHTEEN MILLION
FIVEHUNDRED THOUSAND, UNITED STATES DOLLARS) LEFT IN A LOCAL BANK HERE
IN ABIDJAN. THAT HE USED MY NAME AS HIS ONLY CHILD FOR THE NEXT OF KIN
IN  DEPOSIT OF THE FUND. HE ALSO EXPLAINED TO ME THAT IT WAS BECAUSE OF
THIS WEALTH THAT HE WAS POISONED BY HIS BUSINESS ASSOCIATES, THAT I
SHOULD SEEK FOR A FOREIGN PARTNER IN A COUNTRY OF MY CHOICE WHERE I WILL
TRANSFER THIS MONEY AND USE IT FOR INVESTMENT PURPOSE. (SUCH AS REAL
ESTATE MANAGEMENT). I AM HONOURABLY SEEKING YOUR ASSISTANCE IN THE
FOLLOWING WAYS : TO PROVIDE A BANK ACCOUNT WHERE THIS MONEY WOULD  BE
TRANSFERED TO SERVE AS THE GUARDIAN OF THIS FUND SINCE I AM A GIRL OF 21
YEARS TO MAKE ARRANGEMENT FOR ME TO COME OVER TO YOUR COUNTRY TO FURTHER
MY EDUCATIONAND TO SECURE A RESIDENTIAL PERMIT IN YOUR COUNTRY. I AM
WILLING TO OFFER YOU 30% OF THE TOTAL SUM AS COMPENSATION FOR YOUR!
 
EFFORT INPUT AFTER THE SUCCESSFUL TRANSFER OF THIS FUND TO YOUR
NOMINATED ACCOUNT OVERSEAS . FURTHERMORE, YOU CAN INDICATE YOUR OPTION
TOWARDS ASSISTING ME AS I BELIEVE THAT THIS TRANSACTION WOULD BE
CONCLUDED WITHIN SEVEN (7) DAYS YOU SIGNIFY  INTERESTTO ASSIST ME. I
WILL APPRECIATE YOU SEND ME E-MAIL.

ANTICIPATING TO HEAR FROM YOU
SOON.

THANKS AND GOD BLESS.

JESSICA PRINCE TONY

</pre>



<a shape="rect" href="http://ads.sify.com/RealMedia/ads/click_nx.ads/mail.sify.com/sentmail@Bottom">
<img src="http://ads.sify.com/RealMedia/ads/adstream_nx.ads/mail.sify.com/sentmail@Bottom" width="300" height="40" alt="" /></a>
</body></html>