<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="BUSINESS PROPOSAL" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="&quot; JOHNSON ELENDU &quot; &lt;jelendu@nzoomail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content=" JOHNSON ELENDU  &lt;jelendu@nzoomail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="O" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="jelendu@nzoomail.com" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="R@M" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="R@M" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=us-ascii" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="R@M" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="O" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="BUSINESS PROPOSAL" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-ID" content="&lt;NO01-1-MX001rpwACkW00000224@no01-1-mx001.asp.no01.activeisp.com&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-OriginalArrivalTime" content="02 Jun 2003 23:38:31.0820 (UTC) FILETIME=[138E54C0:01C32960]" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="7bit" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;NO01-1-MX001rpwACkW00000224@no01-1-mx001.asp.no01.activeisp.com&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="&quot; JOHNSON ELENDU &quot; &lt;jelendu@nzoomail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content=" JOHNSON ELENDU  &lt;jelendu@nzoomail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; charset=us-ascii" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="&quot; JOHNSON ELENDU &quot; &lt;jelendu@nzoomail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content=" JOHNSON ELENDU  &lt;jelendu@nzoomail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Mime-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=us-ascii" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="7bit" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;jelendu@nzoomail.com&gt;	by pinkcadillac.mr.itd.UM (3.6u) with ESMTP id h52NrD729061	for &lt;R@M&gt;; Mon, 2 Jun 2003 19:53:14 -0400 (EDT)" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-priority" content="3" />
<meta name="MboxParser-attn" content="sir, " />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Priority" content="3" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-originalarrivaltime" content="02 Jun 2003 23:38:31.0820 (UTC) FILETIME=[138E54C0:01C32960]" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Mon Jun  2 19:53:15 2003" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;jelendu@nzoomail.com&gt; by pinkcadillac.mr.itd.UM (3.6u) with ESMTP id h52NrD729061 for &lt;R@M&gt;; Mon, 2 Jun 2003 19:53:14 -0400 (EDT)" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="JOHNSON ELENDU" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="&quot; JOHNSON ELENDU &quot; &lt;jelendu@nzoomail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="Author" content=" JOHNSON ELENDU  &lt;jelendu@nzoomail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-245" />
<meta name="Message-From" content=" JOHNSON ELENDU  &lt;jelendu@nzoomail.com&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;NO01-1-MX001rpwACkW00000224@no01-1-mx001.asp.no01.activeisp.com&gt;" />
<title>BUSINESS PROPOSAL</title>
</head>
<body><p>PLEASE TREAT AS ABSOLUTELY CONFIDENTIAL 
FROM THE DESK OF JOHNSON ELENDU. 
AUDITING AND ACCOUNTING UNIT. 
FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPT. 
UNION BANK PLC. 
REPLY STRICTLY VIA: [jelendu2@indiatimes.com]
Attn: sir, 

Permit me to introduce myself to you, My name is Johnson Elendu., I am one of the Senior Managers in the bank I work for (Union Bank, Nigeria PLC) and I work under the Director of Foreign Exchange Operations (International Remittance). I am contacting You presently because I need your urgent assistance in a business transaction that will be of immense benefit to both of us. 
I have the immediate need to transfer some money that has long been 
declared "UNCLAIMED" by the chairman and some members of the board of 
directors of our bank. The money is the closing balance of one of our best customers ever, Late Engr. Manfred Becker, I was his personal account officer just before he died in the ADC plane crash of 1996 in Nigeria. 
Engr. Manfred Becker an American citizen was a contractor with the 
Federal Government of Nigeria, he supplied and installed equipment and his company Creek land Contractors completed some of the best construction contracts in the country. His closing balance in the Bank, Union Bank of Nigeria PLC (US$40.Million) has been tagged Unclaimed because no relative of Engr. Becker has come forward to make a statement of claim. We have no knowledge of a next of kin. At this point I trust you can picture what the situation is like. We have strong proof that the chairman and the board of directors will keep most of the money for themselves and donate the remainder to a discredited military trust here in Nigeria. This invariably 
is an attempt to infuse more money into the acquisition of military 
equipment (arms and ammunition) for use in an already prostrate Africa. 
This of course, is senseless, hence my mission. 
My colleagues and my self have made several attempts at locating 
persons that could be remotely related to Engr. Becker and we have been doing this 
for about 4 years now. Right now I am almost alone in this enterprise and I have presently decided on moving the money to a foreign account. I am hereby soliciting your assistance and I will be very grateful if you will be willing to help in this regard. 

We have access to most of what it will take to transfer the money. The only thing we do not have is a safe account. We will provide you with answers to all the security questions, which you will have to answer to move the process towards completion. We will also provide you answers to questions that only a person related to him will know. You may however not need to make any appearance; every thing will be concluded on phone and email between you and the bank [UNION BANK NIGERIA PLC, LAGOS] for your participation you will get 30%, 5% has been earmarked for the expenses that may be incurred on both ends. 65%shall be for my colleague and I. 

I make this proposal in trust and in good faith, therefore, if you are interested and you agree to assist me then contact me immediately you receive this email, there is a lot more to talk about. If you are not interested, then, please, do get rid of this email and please forgive me if this message has upset you in any way. 

Thank you and best regards. 

Mr. JOHNSON ELENDU 
ALTERNATIVE E-MAIL: [jelendu2@indiatimes.com] 

</p>

</body></html>