<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="URGENT REPLY NEEDED" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="barry_k_family@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="barry_k_family@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="O" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2006-06-07T13:52:28Z" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="barry_k_family@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="barry_k_family@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="barry_k_family@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=US-ASCII" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="barry_k_family@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="O" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="URGENT REPLY NEEDED" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="7BIT" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;200606071357.k57Dv1sO006800@brazil.mail.UM&gt; " />
<meta name="creator" content="barry_k_family@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="creator" content="barry_k_family@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; charset=US-ASCII" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="barry_k_family@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="barry_k_family@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2006-06-07T13:52:28Z" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=US-ASCII" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2 HIGHLY CONFIDENTIAL." />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2006-06-07T13:52:28Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="7BIT" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;barry_k_family@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-attention" content="" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Wed Jun  7 09:57:15 2006" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;barry_k_family@yahoo.com&gt; " />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-Id" content="&lt;200606071357.k57Dv1sO006800@brazil.mail.UM&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="barry_k_family@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="Author" content="barry_k_family@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-2657" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="barry_k_family@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;200606071357.k57Dv1sO006800@brazil.mail.UM&gt; " />
<title>URGENT REPLY NEEDED</title>
</head>
<body><p>MR BARRY KABILA
30 VICTORIA STREET, 
JOHANNESBURG, 
SOUTH AFRICA. 
E-MAIL : barrykabila1@yahoo.com                               
                          

                                  HIGHLY CONFIDENTIAL.
ATTENTION: 
 
You may be surprised to receive this message from me since you don't know me in 
person, but for the purpose of introduction, I am MR.Barry Kabila, the son of late 
MR.EKOHANA KABILA, who was murdered in a land dispute in ZIMBABWE. 

I got your contact through the South African International Exchange Network On-line 
here in Johannesburg, South  Africa as reliable and trustworthy to deal with,then I 
decided to write you. My late father was among the few black Zimbabwean rich farmers 
murdered in cold blood by the agent of the ruling government of President ROBERT 
MUGABE for his alleged support and sympathy for Zimbabwean opposition party. 

Before the death of my father, he took me to South Africa to deposit the sum of 
Twenty  Million Five Hundred Thousand US Dollars ($20.5m) with a security and finance 
company, as if he knew the looming danger in Zimbabwe. The money was deposited as a 
gem or precious stone to avoid much demurrage from the security firm. 

This money was earmarked for the purchase of new machinery and chemicals for the 
farms and the establishment of new farms in Lesotho and Swaziland. 

This land problem arose when President R. MUGABE introduced a new land Act. which 
wholly affects the White rich farmers and some few blacks vehemently condemned the 
'MODUS OPERANDI' adopted by the government. This resulted to rampant killing and mob 
actions. 

I and my family who are currently staying in South Africa as a refugee or an asylum 
seeker have decided to transfer this money to a foreign country where we can invest 
it. I am faced with the dilemma of investing this amount of money in South Africa for 
fear of encountering the same experience in future since both countries have the same 
political history. 

Moreover, the South African monetary policy/law does not allow such investment hence I 
am seeking for and asylum or refugee. I must let you know that this business is 100% 
risk free and the nature of your business does not necessarily matter. So if you are 
willing to assist us,I and my family have agreed to give you 20% of the total money, 
35% will be for a joint business venture I will be doing with you and another 40% 
will be for me and my family which we shall also invest in your country and the 
remaining 5% will be mapped out for all expenses we may incurred during the 
transaction. 

Therefore, if you are willing and interested to render the needed assistance, 
endeavor to reply through my email address or the above.I also need your private 
phone and fax number for easy communication. Remember that this is highly 
confidential and the success of this business depends on how secret it is 
kept. 

Expecting your reply soonest. 

Best Regard. 

Mr.Barry Kabila. 
E-MAIL : barrykabila1@yahoo.com 



</p>

</body></html>