<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="MboxParser-x-originating-ip" content="165.228.132.11" />
<meta name="subject" content="YOUR ATTENTION!!" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="Geoffrey Winkler &lt;geo.winkler4@virgilio.it&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="Geoffrey Winkler &lt;geo.winkler4@virgilio.it&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2006-06-14T12:56:37Z" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="geo.winkler4@virgilio.it" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="geo.winkler4@virgilio.it" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="geo.winkler4@virgilio.it" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain;charset=&quot;UTF-8&quot;" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="geo.winkler4@virgilio.it" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="MboxParser-reply-to" content="g.alabasten@virgilio.it" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Reply-To" content="g.alabasten@virgilio.it" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="YOUR ATTENTION!!" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="7bit" />
<meta name="creator" content="Geoffrey Winkler &lt;geo.winkler4@virgilio.it&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="Geoffrey Winkler &lt;geo.winkler4@virgilio.it&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain;charset=&quot;UTF-8&quot;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="Geoffrey Winkler &lt;geo.winkler4@virgilio.it&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="Geoffrey Winkler &lt;geo.winkler4@virgilio.it&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2006-06-14T12:56:37Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Mime-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain;charset=&quot;UTF-8&quot;" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2006-06-14T12:56:37Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="7bit" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;geo.winkler4@virgilio.it&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Wed Jun 14 09:06:51 2006" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;geo.winkler4@virgilio.it&gt; Alternative E-Mail to ---&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="Geoffrey Winkler" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="Geoffrey Winkler &lt;geo.winkler4@virgilio.it&gt;" />
<meta name="Author" content="Geoffrey Winkler &lt;geo.winkler4@virgilio.it&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Originating-IP" content="165.228.132.11" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-2682" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="Geoffrey Winkler &lt;geo.winkler4@virgilio.it&gt;" />
<title>YOUR ATTENTION!!</title>
</head>
<body><p>Dear Associate,

I wish to use this medium to reach out to you and at 
the same time strongly advice that you endeavore to treat and consider 
this mail confidential and urgent.

My name is Geoffrey Winkler; i am 
the personal account officer to one Engineer B.Williams a foreign 
expatriate with Mobil Petroleum Company here in Netherlands. My client 
was one of those involved in the Alaska airline flight 261-plane crash 
that took place February of 2000, which claimed the lives of every 
passengers on board.

My client had operated an account here with 
FINANS BANK (Netherlands) valued at 8.5m euros. This funds he amassed 
out of his proficient services with this company, his account have 
remained dormant and unclaimed since after his death possibly b'cos he 
kept it private and as a result of being dormant for a long time the 
bank management have resolved to enforce it's banking regulations 
having considered this account inactive and in view have indicated it's 
interest to divert the floating funds into the bank treasury as 
unclaimed funds within the next ( 21 ) official working days. Since all 
this time i have been expecting the next of kin to my deceased client 
to come over and claim and receive payment of this funds here in the 
custody of the bank since the banking laws stipulates that in such 
situation the money can only be released to the next of kin but 
surprisingly no next of kin have made any such claims of this funds or 
identified. This situation prompted me to have personally made several 
enquiries in order to possibly contact his next of kin but it only led 
me to discover that his supposed next of kin were among those in the 
plane crash leaving nobody for the claims.

As this situation 
imperatively damands a next of kin to file claims of this funds, i am 
contacting you as a foreigner which is of my best intention to possibly 
identifying you to help claim and receive payment of this money here in 
the custody of the bank presenting as the next of kin for safe keeping 
and for future investment  before the funds is confisticated and 
diverted into the bank treasury as unclaimed funds.

I will be counting 
on your reputation as being reliable for this transaction,as you can be 
rest assured of the full representation of your interest here as will 
be required to have this money released and paid to you. Do understand 
this transaction is 100% risk free and is in no way associated with 
money laundering, so on gaining your interest to proceed as will be 
required to receive payment of this money presenting as the next of kin 
then we can further discuss on the modalities for disbursing of the 
money.

I anticipate your kind and prompt response with your telephone 
numbers with best time to reach you and your full names and contact 
address to enable me highlight you further.
 Alternative E-Mail to ---&gt; 
c_info@virgilio.it 

Please do understand that my contacting you is for 
our good interest and benefit as i sure hope you will be of good 
assistance. Thanks,

Geoffrey Winkler.



</p>

</body></html>