<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="URGENT REPLY NEEDED!!!" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="&quot;Alhaji Yusuf A&quot; &lt;yusuf_adamah@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="Alhaji Yusuf A &lt;yusuf_adamah@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="O" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="yusuf_adamah@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2006-08-20T00:32:28Z" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="aiweb06@cs.umbc.edu" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="aiweb06@cs.umbc.edu" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;us-ascii&quot;" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="aiweb06@cs.umbc.edu" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="O" />
<meta name="MboxParser-reply-to" content="yusuf_adamah@excite.com" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Reply-To" content="yusuf_adamah@excite.com" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="URGENT REPLY NEEDED!!!" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;200606192331.k5JNVmZO024417@mailserver-ng.cs.umbc.edu&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="&quot;Alhaji Yusuf A&quot; &lt;yusuf_adamah@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="Alhaji Yusuf A &lt;yusuf_adamah@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;us-ascii&quot;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="&quot;Alhaji Yusuf A&quot; &lt;yusuf_adamah@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="Alhaji Yusuf A &lt;yusuf_adamah@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2006-08-20T00:32:28Z" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;us-ascii&quot;" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2006-08-20T00:32:28Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;yusuf_adamah@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-mailer" content="Microsoft Outlook Express 5.00.2919.6900 DM" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Mon Jun 19 19:32:16 2006" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;yusuf_adamah@yahoo.com&gt; " />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-Id" content="&lt;200606192331.k5JNVmZO024417@mailserver-ng.cs.umbc.edu&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="Alhaji Yusuf A" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="&quot;Alhaji Yusuf A&quot; &lt;yusuf_adamah@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="Author" content="Alhaji Yusuf A &lt;yusuf_adamah@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Mailer" content="Microsoft Outlook Express 5.00.2919.6900 DM" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-2712" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="Alhaji Yusuf A &lt;yusuf_adamah@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;200606192331.k5JNVmZO024417@mailserver-ng.cs.umbc.edu&gt;" />
<title>URGENT REPLY NEEDED!!!</title>
</head>
<body><p>Dear Friend,

Let me start by introducing myself properly to you. I
am Alhaji Yusuf Adamah, I work with the United Bank
for Africa UBA as an account officer in the Treasury/
Credit Control Unit. I came to know you in private search
for a reliable and reputable person to handle this confidential
transaction, which involve the transfer of a huge sum of
money into a foriegn account requiring maximum confidence.

I must solicit your confidence in this transaction, by virtue of
its nature that is utterly confidential and secret. Though I know
that a transaction of this magnitude will make any one
apprehensive and worried, but I am assuring you that all will be
well at the end of the day. I decided to contact you due to the
fact that this transaction is urgent, as I will rely on your ability in
handling a transaction of this nature.

THE NATURE OF THE PROPOSITION / TRANSACTION:
A foreigner by name Andreas Schranner , who is a real
estate and property developer by profession executed certain
contract/supply with the Government of the Federal Republic
of Nigeria in 1998. The payment for the executed contract had
been approved and deposited with our bank in an Escrow account
with us at UBA and had a closing balance as at the end of January
2000, which is worth ($27M) Twenty seven Million United States Dollars.

I was his personal account officer and since the government deposited
this money with us in the year 1999, We were instructed by my late
client that the money be kept and secured in a security and finance firm
because it was less expensive to keep and secure the funds in the
security firm devoid of tax payments.

I am sad to inform you that Mr Andreas Schranner, his wife, daughter,
daughter inlaw and children died in the ill fated concorde flight AF4590
that crashed into Hotelisimmo on the 31st of July 2000 in Paris-France.
Check this website below:

http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/europe/859479.stm

Our bank now expects his Next of Kin to come forward as a sole
beneficiary to his assets with the bank as accordingto banking laws,
such fund which has stayed more than 5 years without any claim will be
terminated and be used by the bank as unclaimed fund. Mean while, as is
personal account officer valuable efforts has being made by me for more than
three years to get in touch with any of my late client family or relatives without
any success.It is because of the percieved impossibility of being able to locate
any of my late client Next of Kin as his wife Maria Schranner and his daughter
Eich Andreas perished in the flight also.

Based on this, I secretly seek advice from a fellow coleague who has being in
banking for about 14 years now about this issue of my late client , he made me
understand that things like this do happen and at the end of the day the chairman
and board of directors of the bank will declare the funds as '' Unclaimed '' and
subsequently divert it for thier personal use. In order to avert this negetive
development, I now seek your permission to have you stand as the Next of Kin
to my late client, so that the funds will be released and paid into your account as
the beneficiary Next of Kin.

I have already secured from the probate, as soon as I recieve an acknowledgement
of your acceptance, I will furnish you with the necessary modalities of the transaction.
I assure you that this transcaction is 100% risk free, and as soon as we succeed in
getting this funds to your account, I shall take a trip to meet with you in your country
and the money will be shared on a 85% for me and 15% for you. We could go into
joint investment based on your advice.

Please forward to me on acceptance of this proposal, your private telephone and fax
number including the country code and area codes, your complete names,and
private email address for effective communication as the project will be completed
within the next 14 working days.

Please, treat with absolute maturity, kindness and reservation even though you are
not interested to work with me, waiting to hear from you soonest.

Thanks for your anticipated response.

Best Regards.

Alhaji.Y.Adamah



















</p>

</body></html>