<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="FROM: Ms Nasrinn N.Farooq" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="&quot;Ms Nasrinn N.Farooq&quot; &lt;sedattz01@yahoo.es&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="Ms Nasrinn N.Farooq &lt;sedattz01@yahoo.es&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-http" content="//www.cbsnews.com/stories/1999/11/01/iran/main49778.shtml" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="sedattz01@yahoo.es" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2006-07-11T09:45:28Z" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="R@M" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="R@M" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=iso-8859-1" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="R@M" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="MboxParser-reply-to" content="sedattz04@yahoo.es" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Multipart-Boundary" content="fa73b152-c957-43e2-bdc7-5195ec233ec5" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Reply-To" content="sedattz04@yahoo.es" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="FROM: Ms Nasrinn N.Farooq" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;200607110945.k6B9jTmW010068@flawless.mail.UM&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="&quot;Ms Nasrinn N.Farooq&quot; &lt;sedattz01@yahoo.es&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="Ms Nasrinn N.Farooq &lt;sedattz01@yahoo.es&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="&quot;Ms Nasrinn N.Farooq&quot; &lt;sedattz01@yahoo.es&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="Ms Nasrinn N.Farooq &lt;sedattz01@yahoo.es&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2006-07-11T09:45:28Z" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=iso-8859-1" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2006-07-11T09:45:28Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;sedattz01@yahoo.es&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Tue Jul 11 05:45:34 2006" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;sedattz01@yahoo.es&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-Id" content="&lt;200607110945.k6B9jTmW010068@flawless.mail.UM&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="Ms Nasrinn N.Farooq" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="&quot;Ms Nasrinn N.Farooq&quot; &lt;sedattz01@yahoo.es&gt;" />
<meta name="Author" content="Ms Nasrinn N.Farooq &lt;sedattz01@yahoo.es&gt;" />
<meta name="Multipart-Subtype" content="mixed" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-2825" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="Ms Nasrinn N.Farooq &lt;sedattz01@yahoo.es&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;200607110945.k6B9jTmW010068@flawless.mail.UM&gt;" />
<title>FROM: Ms Nasrinn N.Farooq</title>
</head>
<body><div class="email-entry"><p><p>My Dear Friend,
I got your contact through a desperate and personal search on the web for someone I could really trust as I have prayed over it and I wish to express my interest to handle this matter with you as Ibelieve that you are reliable in handling these type of international transaction.

Though we have not met before but I believe one has to risk confiding in someone to succeed sometimes in life but however is not mandatory or in any manner compel you to Honor against your will.

Although I am not suppose to contact you through email but it is because of the confidential nature of this transaction please bear with me

I am Ms Nasrinn N.Farooq, a top bank official in the National Bank of Dubai,(UNITED ARAB EMIRATES).

I am writing this letter to ask for your support and co-operation to carry out this business opportunity in my department.

On June 6, 1999,an Oil consultant/contractor with Dubai Petroleum Corporation, MR DAVID AMEERALY, made a numbered time(fixed)deposit for twelve calendar months,Valued at US$16,500, 000.00 (sixteen Million Five Hundred Thousand Dollars) in my branch. upon maturity I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply.

After a month,we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers,the Dubai Petroleum Corporation that MR DAVID AMEERALY, died in the plane crash On October 31,1999,(an Egyptian Boeing767Flight 990) with other passengers on board as you can confirm it yourself via the website below:
http://www.cbsnews.com/stories/1999/11/01/iran/main49778.shtml

On further investigation,I found out that he died without making a WILL and attempts to trace his next of kin were fruitless .I therefore made further investigation and discovered that MR DAVID AMEERALY,did not declare any next of kin or relations in all his official documents,including his bank deposit paperwork in my bank.

This sum of US$16,500, 000.00 and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year.No one will ever come forward to claim it and according to UNITED ARAB EMIRATES LAW,at the expiration of(Ten) years,the money will revert to the ownership of the UNITED ARAB EMIRATES Government if nobody applies to claim the fund.

My proposal is that I will like you to stand as the next of kin to MR DAVID AMEERALY, so that the fruit of this old man labour will not get into the hands of some corrupt Government officials.This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full name and address so that I can forward to you the contact of our bank Attorney for preparing the necessary documents and affidavits which will put you in place as the next of kin.

Any bank account in any part of the world,which you will provide,will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin.

The money will be paid into your account for us to share in ratio of  45% for me and 45% for you and 10 % will be set aside for expenses in cured during the business.There is no risk at all.

The paperwork for this transaction will be done by the attorney and my position as the Branch Manager guarantees the successful execution of  this transaction.

If you are interested,please reply immediately and upon your responses,I shall provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction.

Please observe utmost confidentiality and be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country.

Please upon the receipt of this mail message,send to me the following below to enable me start the processing of the transfer,

1.Your Full Name
2.Your House Address.
3.Your Phone Number and Fax,

Thank You And God Bless You.

Sincerely,

Ms Nasrinn N.Farooq</p>

</p>
</div>
</body></html>