<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="MboxParser-x-senderip" content="64.201.33.31" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-terra-hash" content="d3cb48349abde64c23fc24978dd5b3ba mother are seeking&lt;BR&gt;asylum in South Africa under (UNHCR).&lt;/DIV&gt;" />
<meta name="subject" content="GET BACK TO ME" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="Frank Siaka " />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="2katherine &lt;2katherine@terra.com.mx&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sensitivity" content="3 my arrival to meet with you for&lt;BR&gt;investing of the money with any profi=" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="2katherine@terra.com.mx" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2006-07-27T15:04:22Z" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="undisclosed-recipients:;" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="undisclosed-recipients:;" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="multipart/alternative; entirely.&lt;/DIV&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sensitivity" content="3" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-terra-karma" content="0% to leave&lt;BR&gt;the country with a very important document of (US$ 7,650,000=" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Multipart-Boundary" content="_=__=_XaM3_.1154012662.2A.694789.42.22851.52.42.007.679615548" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="GET BACK TO ME" />
<meta name="MboxParser-&lt;div&gt;from" content="Frank Siaka &lt;BR&gt;+27 73 260 3786&lt;/DIV&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-SenderIP" content="64.201.33.31" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;J32HVA$814C79952D37246ACBEA8F789BCAF4B7@terra.com.mx&gt; 28yrs, I am confused on&lt;BR&gt;how to handle this huge amount of money and a=" />
<meta name="creator" content="Frank Siaka " />
<meta name="creator" content="2katherine &lt;2katherine@terra.com.mx&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="Frank Siaka " />
<meta name="meta:author" content="2katherine &lt;2katherine@terra.com.mx&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2006-07-27T15:04:22Z" />
<meta name="format" content="multipart/alternative; entirely.&lt;/DIV&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.2 boundary=&quot;_=__=_XaM3_.1154012662.2A.694789.42.22851.52.42.007.679615548&quot; soon&lt;BR&gt;as I get your response I shall give out more details on how we s=" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2006-07-27T15:04:22Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-XaM3-API-Version" content="4.1 (B108)" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;2katherine@terra.com.mx&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Terra-Karma" content="         0%" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Terra-Hash" content="d3cb48349abde64c23fc24978dd5b3ba	Thu, 27 Jul 2006 11:04:22 -0400 (EDT)" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Thu Jul 27 11:04:51 2006" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;2katherine@terra.com.mx&gt; Thu, 27 Jul 2006 11:04:22 -0400 (EDT) country as&lt;BR&gt;being economic conducive for investment and her people as =" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-Id" content="&lt;J32HVA$814C79952D37246ACBEA8F789BCAF4B7@terra.com.mx&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0 my&lt;BR&gt;father left behind, of which my name appears as the &quot;Next Of Kin=94=" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="2katherine" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="Frank Siaka " />
<meta name="Author" content="2katherine &lt;2katherine@terra.com.mx&gt;" />
<meta name="Multipart-Subtype" content="alternative" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-xam3-api-version" content="4.1 (B108)" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-2881" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="2katherine &lt;2katherine@terra.com.mx&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;J32HVA$814C79952D37246ACBEA8F789BCAF4B7@terra.com.mx&gt; 28yrs, I am confused on&lt;BR&gt;how to handle this huge amount of money and a=" />
<title>GET BACK TO ME</title>
</head>
<body>
From: Frank Siaka 
+27 73 260 3786

Dear Sir, 

I should appreciate your surprise while receiving this letter. In any
case,I am left with no option but to contact you in this manner. my
decision to
write to you was informed by knowledge that being established personally
that you could be disposed to understand my predicament in order to give me
the assistance I require I am Frank Siaka the son of a late Sierra-Leonian
businessman, late Dr.Coleman Siaka the owner of (RMS) Mining Company in
Sierra-Leone, who died few years ago when the Revolutionary United Front
Rebels (R.U.F) attacked our residence on the 11 of Feb. 2004 in Makeni
Sierra-Leone.

Following the cease fire agreement which was reached last year with the
help of United Nation peace keeping troops, I used the opportunity to leave
the country with a very important document of (US$ 7,650,000.00) Seven
Million Six Hundred and Fifty Thousand United States Dollars, deposited by
my late father in Security Company in South Africa, under my name. This
money was realized from diamond export, now I and my mother are seeking
asylum in South Africa under (UNHCR).

I contacted you because of the need to deal with person whom my family and
I have no previous personal relationships, and I confirmed your country as
being economic conducive for investment and her people as transparent and
trust-worthy to engage in business, hence my reason for writing you
however, this money in question has been in the security company since his
death. But my main problem now is that at my age of 28yrs, I am confused on
how to handle this huge amount of money and also what to do with it as I
don't have anyone to confide in South Africa here. May I use this medium to
request from you if you will be disposed enough to help me keep this huge
amount in your country or any other place of your choice that will have
more security to the money and the life of me and my family?

I have met the security company with the depositional documents that my
father left behind, of which my name appears as the "Next Of Kin”, the
company awaits my coming for the withdrawal, and I am even afraid of
disclosing the content to them since my father in his letter had warned me
against that.
If it appeals to you to help me, I will suggest you take a trip to South
Africa for us to meet face to face and finalize before moving the fund or
if there is any other means you can suggest for the transferring of the
fund to your very position pending my arrival to meet with you for
investing of the money with any profitable business you introduce, as I
have decided to do away with Africa entirely.

I want immediate confirmation of your through our e-mail address. As soon
as I get your response I shall give out more details on how we shall
proceed. Kindly keep this proposal strictly confidential because of our
present status here in South Africa.

Thanks and remain blessed. I wait to receive a favorable response from you
urgently.

Yours faithfully, 
Frank Siaka

 

 


</body></html>