<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="MboxParser-x-originating-ip" content="194.126.179.100" />
<meta name="subject" content="PLZ SAVE MY LIFE" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="&quot;mercyyatteh@adinet.com.uy&quot; &lt;mercyyatteh@adinet.com.uy&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="mercyyatteh@adinet.com.uy &lt;mercyyatteh@adinet.com.uy&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2006-08-30T03:04:49Z" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="mercyyatteh@adinet.com.uy" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain;charset=&quot;ISO-8859-15&quot;" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="undisclosed-recipients: ;" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="undisclosed-recipients:;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="MboxParser-reply-to" content="mercyatteh@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-ID" content="&lt;11964314.1156907089773.JavaMail.tomcat@fe-ps01&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Reply-To" content="mercyatteh@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="PLZ SAVE MY LIFE" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.3" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="7bit" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;11964314.1156907089773.JavaMail.tomcat@fe-ps01&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="&quot;mercyyatteh@adinet.com.uy&quot; &lt;mercyyatteh@adinet.com.uy&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="mercyyatteh@adinet.com.uy &lt;mercyyatteh@adinet.com.uy&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain;charset=&quot;ISO-8859-15&quot;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="&quot;mercyyatteh@adinet.com.uy&quot; &lt;mercyyatteh@adinet.com.uy&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="mercyyatteh@adinet.com.uy &lt;mercyyatteh@adinet.com.uy&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2006-08-30T03:04:49Z" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.3" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain;charset=&quot;ISO-8859-15&quot;" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2006-08-30T03:04:49Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="7bit" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;mercyyatteh@adinet.com.uy&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Tue Aug 29 23:18:49 2006" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;mercyyatteh@adinet.com.uy&gt; I and the lawyer is the only one aware of this money, so I have" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="&quot;mercyyatteh@adinet.com.uy&quot; &lt;mercyyatteh@adinet.com.uy&gt;" />
<meta name="Author" content="mercyyatteh@adinet.com.uy &lt;mercyyatteh@adinet.com.uy&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Originating-IP" content="194.126.179.100" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-2970" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="mercyyatteh@adinet.com.uy &lt;mercyyatteh@adinet.com.uy&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;11964314.1156907089773.JavaMail.tomcat@fe-ps01&gt;" />
<title>PLZ SAVE MY LIFE</title>
</head>
<body><p>My Dear,

I greet you in the name of our lord Jesus Christ. My name is Mrs.Mercy 
Atteh I am a widow and a mother of three all girls. I know you will see 
my letter to you as an embarrassment considering the fact that we do 
not know ourselves. I plead with you to be patient with me I feel very 
pleased to contact you for some assistance and business relationship. I 
live in Nigeria with my children. My late husband was a loving, caring 
and hardworking businessman who died unfortunately In a ghastly auto 
crash. Before the sudden death of my beloved husband, and father of my 
daughters, my late husband intended to establish a business in the 
united states of America with the sum of$30 million united states 
dollars, but unfortunately he died before this proposed venture. 
Following his death, his family members insisted that I am not entitled 
to his property (Assets and money) since I am a woman and my 
offspring's all girls as I do not have a male child for my husband. 
Well, according to some barbaric traditional laws here in Nigeria 
(Africa) which doesn't permit a woman to inherit a man's property, as 
they are expected by tradition to take over the management of his 
business and other properties including myself who automatically 
becomes a wife to one of his immediate brothers. Unfortunately to this 
wicked family members, the $30million united states dollars which my 
late husband intended to use in establishing a business in the United 
States was deposited in a bank account unknown to his family .

 I and the lawyer is the only one aware of this money, so I have 
discussed this matter with a staff of the bank that i want this money 
personally so that I will be able to take care of my children's 
educational needs since my husband's family members vehemently opposed 
the furtherance of their education. According to the staff of the bank, 
the best way to secure this money is to transfer this money to a bank 
account outside Nigeria For safe-keeping, later it will be used for 
business establishment subject to the Advise of whosoever finally 
assists us. At this juncture, I there fore ask for your sincere 
assistance in providing us with your bank details and the enablement to 
facilitate the remittance of this fund into your nominated account. As 
soon as I get your positive response, I shall provide you with all the 
necessary detail for this transfer. However, I have decided to to give 
you 20% of the total money as a reward for your sincere assistance and 
the remaining 65% of the money will be for my investment as I will want 
to keep aglow my late husbands dream of investing in real estate. To be 
able to help me, kindly send through my email, your personal details 
including your contact information for easy communication. 

Thanking you for your anticipated response 
Mrs. Mercy Atteh. 



</p>

</body></html>