<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="Try and get back to me." />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="&quot;Mr.Abdull Nasser&quot; &lt;cheik_bello@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="Mr.Abdull Nasser &lt;cheik_bello@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="cheik_bello@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2006-12-04T19:45:27Z" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="R@M" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="R@M" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;us-ascii&quot;" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="R@M" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="MboxParser-reply-to" content="abdull.nasser@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Reply-To" content="abdull.nasser@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="Try and get back to me." />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.3" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;200612041945.kB4Jjm1I010652@chaos.mail.UM&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="&quot;Mr.Abdull Nasser&quot; &lt;cheik_bello@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="Mr.Abdull Nasser &lt;cheik_bello@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;us-ascii&quot;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="&quot;Mr.Abdull Nasser&quot; &lt;cheik_bello@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="Mr.Abdull Nasser &lt;cheik_bello@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2006-12-04T19:45:27Z" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.3" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;us-ascii&quot;" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2006-12-04T19:45:27Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;cheik_bello@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-mailer" content="Microsoft Outlook Express 5.00.2919.6900 DM" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Mon Dec  4 14:45:54 2006" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;cheik_bello@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-Id" content="&lt;200612041945.kB4Jjm1I010652@chaos.mail.UM&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="Mr.Abdull Nasser" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="&quot;Mr.Abdull Nasser&quot; &lt;cheik_bello@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="Author" content="Mr.Abdull Nasser &lt;cheik_bello@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Mailer" content="Microsoft Outlook Express 5.00.2919.6900 DM" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-3326" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="Mr.Abdull Nasser &lt;cheik_bello@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;200612041945.kB4Jjm1I010652@chaos.mail.UM&gt;" />
<title>Try and get back to me.</title>
</head>
<body><p>Dear sir,
URGENT AND CONFIDENTIAL
--------------------------
I write to introduce this important business opportunity to you irespective of the fact that we
have not seen or known each other before but I believe that it will be of immense benefit to both
of us.Let me formally introduce myself. I am Mr.ABDULLAH NASSER, a Manager of one of the Apex bank here. I got
your particulars in my earnst search for a reliable individual who can assist me in this
transaction, with the belief in God that you will never let me down.There is an outstanding sum of US$10.2,Million(
Ten million two hundred thousand United States Dollars)belonging to late Mr.Andreas B.Smith, a foreigner and miner in the
Kruger Gold Co. a geologist by profession. This fund was deposited since 2000 by the deacesed and since
2002 nobody has operated the said account. After going through some old files in the records, I
discovered that the owner of this dormant account Mr.Andreas B. Simth does no longer exist and that if
I do not remit this fund out urgently, it would be forfeited for nothing.

I am contacting you because of the need to involve a foreigner with foreign account and foreign
beneficiary. I need your full co-operation to make this work out fine because the management is ready
to approve this payment to a foreigner, who has the correct information of this account which I will
provide to you. Should this interest you, kindly furnish me with your overseas bank account details
including your private phone and fax number for easy comunication.
With my position now in the office, I can arrange for the transfer of this fund to any foreign
reliable account which you can provide with assurance that this money will be intact pending my
physical arrival in your country for sharing. I will destroy all documents of transaction immediately
you recieve this fund leaving no trace to any place. and will also use my position and influence
to effect legal approvals and onward transfer of the money to your account with appropriate clearance
forms of ministries and foreign exchange departments.

I have resolved to compensate you by offering a brokerage commission of 20% net pre-transfer
expenses you may incure, 5% set aside for general expenses 75% will be for me and I guarantee that
all expenses during the transfer are subject to refund.
Most importantly, I must emphasize that this business requires utmost confidentiality and trust.
We need to go into an agreement that will bind us together and the same will protect our individual
interest in the near future. I will apply for annual leave to get a Visa for a trip to your country once
this money is transferred into your foreign account.In recognition of your personal executive power and
investment opportunities that is abound in your country, do know that I have in mind to establish a
genuine business relationship with you in the nearest future, if you will be able to help me. In
order to expedite action, let me recieve your approval or reply through the above phone numbers
or by e-mail.Please accept my compliments, as I await for your
kind response.
Yours Sincerely,
Mr.ABDULLAH NASSER




</p>

</body></html>