<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="dc:creator" content="mrs_sm001@sify.com" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="mrs_sm001@sify.com" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="mrs_sm001@sify.com" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/html" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Multipart-Boundary" content="-MOQ1168417198cae30143d0d9d757c75fecfea5e31005" />
<meta name="MboxParser-email" content="barrister_tunde234@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="MboxParser-email" content="&lt;br&gt;barrister_tunde234@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.3	(envelope-from mrs_sm001@sify.com)	(envelope-from mrs_sm001@sify.com)" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="8bit" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="8bit" />
<meta name="creator" content="mrs_sm001@sify.com" />
<meta name="creator" content="mrs_sm001@sify.com" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="mrs_sm001@sify.com" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="mrs_sm001@sify.com" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.3 (envelope-from mrs_sm001@sify.com)" />
<meta name="format" content="text/html" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;mrs_sm001@sify.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Wed Jan 10 04:07:30 2007" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;mrs_sm001@sify.com&gt; (envelope-from mrs_sm001@sify.com)" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="mrs_sm001@sify.com" />
<meta name="Author" content="mrs_sm001@sify.com" />
<meta name="Multipart-Subtype" content="alternative" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-3428" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="mrs_sm001@sify.com" />
<title></title>
</head>
<body><pre>





Friend in the Lord,



Please use this money for the churches and
less privileged.



Greetings to you and your family in the name of God.
In my search for a reliable and God fearing person and having gotten
your contact through prayers and painstaking efforts I have decided to
seek your help in carrying out my last wishes. My name is Mrs.Marvis
Smith. I'm a 65 years old woman and from Congo. I was a merchant and
owned two businesses in Dubai. I was also married with two
children.



My husband and two children died in a car accident six
years ago. Before this happened, my business and concern for making
money was all I live for. I never really cared about other values in
life. But since the loss of my family, I have found a new desire to
assist helpless families. I have been helping orphans in
orphanage/motherless homes. I have also donated some money for
humanitarian needs in Sudan, South Africa, Cameroon, Brazil, Spain,
Austria, Germany and some Asian countries. Only recently I saw on
television the colossal loss of properties and livelihood people in
Canberra, Australia through fire.



I was moving with great pity and
compassion that I decided to make this contribution on assisting people
over there, I kept $US25,000,000.00 Million in a long-term deposit
account in a Finance company. Presently, I'm in a hospital where I have
been undergoing treatment for oesophagi cancer. I have since lost my
ability to talk and my doctors have told me that I have only few months
to live. It is my last wish to see this money distributed to victims of
the fire outbreak in Australia and other charity organization. Because
relatives and friends have plundered so much of my wealth since my
illness, I cannot live with the agony entrusting this huge
responsibility to any of them.



Please, I beg you in the name of God
to help me collect the deposit and  distributes it accordingly. Use your
judgment to distribute the money and keep 20% of it to yourself. Feel
free to reimburse yourself when you have the money for any cost you
incur during the process of collecting and distributing the money. If
you are willing to help, please reply as soon as possible. May the good
lord bless you and your family.



Please, send reply and all
correspondences to my attorney :

Barrister. Lamo benson

Email:
barrister_tunde234@yahoo.com





Regards,



mrs_sm011@yahoo.com

Mrs.M
arvis Smith

</pre>




<a shape="rect" href="http://ads.sify.com/RealMedia/ads/click_nx.ads/mail.sify.com/sentmail@Bottom">
<img src="http://ads.sify.com/RealMedia/ads/adstream_nx.ads/mail.sify.com/sentmail@Bottom" width="300" height="40" alt="" /></a>

Watch latest movie trailers and behind the scenes footage of Bigg Boss and Zee Cine Stars and much more! <a shape="rect" href="http://www.sifymax.com/">www.sifymax.com</a>

See what's happening in your favourite City on Mumbai Live! <a shape="rect" href="http://www.mumbailive.in/">www.mumbailive.in</a>
</body></html>