<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="Re: Please confirm receipt." />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="&quot;Abu Kyari.&quot; &lt;akyari1@sudanmail.net.sd&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="Abu Kyari. &lt;akyari1@sudanmail.net.sd&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-http" content="//www.sudanet.net" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="akyari1@sudanmail.net.sd" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2003-07-31T06:38:14Z" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="akyari1@sudanmail.net.sd" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="akyari1@sudanmail.net.sd" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;windows-1256&quot;; format=&quot;flowed&quot;" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="akyari1@sudanmail.net.sd" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="Re: Please confirm receipt." />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-ID" content="&lt;web-8213587@sudanmail.net&gt;" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="8bit" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;web-8213587@sudanmail.net&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="&quot;Abu Kyari.&quot; &lt;akyari1@sudanmail.net.sd&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="Abu Kyari. &lt;akyari1@sudanmail.net.sd&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;windows-1256&quot;; format=&quot;flowed&quot;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="&quot;Abu Kyari.&quot; &lt;akyari1@sudanmail.net.sd&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="Abu Kyari. &lt;akyari1@sudanmail.net.sd&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2003-07-31T06:38:14Z" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;windows-1256&quot;; format=&quot;flowed&quot;" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2003-07-31T06:38:14Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="8bit" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;akyari1@sudanmail.net.sd&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-mailer" content="CommuniGate Pro Web Mailer v.4.0.6" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Thu Jul 31 01:52:41 2003" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;akyari1@sudanmail.net.sd&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="Abu Kyari." />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="&quot;Abu Kyari.&quot; &lt;akyari1@sudanmail.net.sd&gt;" />
<meta name="Author" content="Abu Kyari. &lt;akyari1@sudanmail.net.sd&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Mailer" content="CommuniGate Pro Web Mailer v.4.0.6" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-341" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="Abu Kyari. &lt;akyari1@sudanmail.net.sd&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;web-8213587@sudanmail.net&gt;" />
<title>Re: Please confirm receipt.</title>
</head>
<body><p>Greetings and Compliments.

I have gotten your contact from the internet, listed as a 
professional 
whom I might be able to transact with, and this makes me 
feel I may 
make a sincere proposition to you, and I have decided to 
make this preposition to you in good faith, which relates 
to a realistic and genuinely simplistic business opening 
that needs the participation of a person with your 
expertise, and ingenuity and a clear indication to
trustworthiness and sincerity.

I am a lawyer residing and practicing in Nigeria as you 
may need to know and I represent the interest of a client 
who is a Brother as well who has made an offer to me which 
is most lucrative, my correspondence with you from hence 
is dictated by the need for us to get the participation of 
a neutral foreigner who will assist us perfect the 
transaction.

My client was a prominent figure in the Military Politics 
and rule of 
my country for about ten years and he has had complicity 
in a few economic scandals and a host of litigations too 
he has had a lot of his physical and monetary assets 
seized by the Nigerian Government who consider him as a 
part of the corrupt machinery of the then Military 
Government. Now he has a substantial amount deposited in a 
bank in Nigeria (US$ 25.M.) and he is very scared that 
this account will be discovered because similar accounts 
in Switzerland and England were previously discovered and 
frozen by the governments of those countries in 
collaboration with the Government of Nigeria.

Precisely, my client's family returned US$ 1B. to the 
government of Nigeria in 2002 under the direction of the 
Swiss banking authorities, this is a confirmable matter, 
even as the existence of the fund mentioned above is 
confirmable. 

Now it is his intention to migrate with his family out of 
Nigeria 
towards the Middle East and he depends so much on this 
fund, thus he is
looking for a reliable and trustworthy person who will 
receive the money
discreetly and then transfer the money at a latter date to 
a neutral account to be established in Lebanon when he 
finally succeeds with his emigration plan.

If you accept my proposition and agree to participate in 
this 
transaction, you will in no case whatsoever undertake 
risk- expend 
money or execute any unreasonable task- whereas you will 
be well remunerated, in principle you will receive 10% of 
the amount transferred to you once the transaction is 
completed.

Apart from this there is another sum of Money, held up in 
a Security 
Company (In Cash), the Money was earmarked for the support 
of the cause of Charity in India, but it was never 
retrieved before the demise 
of my clients father, now my client also wants to retrieve 
this money in addition to the money with the bank in 
Nigeria. The money with the Security Company is Thirty one 
Million American Dollars in one hundred dollar bills.

Since I do not know in what vein you will take this 
missive I have kept 
the information peripheral, I will be posited to give 
further information upon your acceptance and will also 
introduce you to my client eventually.  I hope I will be 
able to work with you earnestly unto our joint success.

I await your response eagerly.

Respectfully.

Abu Kyari esquire.
Welcome to Sudan pioneer ISP
http://www.sudanet.net


</p>

</body></html>