<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="From: Lady Peggy Morrison," />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="&quot;From: Lady Peggy Morrison,&quot; &lt;jenni@reedtribe.org&gt; When my late husband was alive he deposited the sum of 20  Million (20Mi=" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="From: Lady Peggy Morrison, &lt;jenni@reedtribe.org&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="jenni@reedtribe.org" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;iso-8859-1&quot; " />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="MboxParser-reply-to" content="ladypeggymorrisonoffice14@yahoo.com.hk " />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="From: Lady Peggy Morrison," />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Reply-To" content="ladypeggymorrisonoffice14@yahoo.com.hk" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.3" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="quoted-printable " />
<meta name="creator" content="&quot;From: Lady Peggy Morrison,&quot; &lt;jenni@reedtribe.org&gt; When my late husband was alive he deposited the sum of 20  Million (20Mi=" />
<meta name="creator" content="From: Lady Peggy Morrison, &lt;jenni@reedtribe.org&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;iso-8859-1&quot;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="&quot;From: Lady Peggy Morrison,&quot; &lt;jenni@reedtribe.org&gt; When my late husband was alive he deposited the sum of 20  Million (20Mi=" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="From: Lady Peggy Morrison, &lt;jenni@reedtribe.org&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.3 " />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;iso-8859-1&quot; " />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;jenni@reedtribe.org&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Mon Jan 15 10:06:12 2007" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;jenni@reedtribe.org&gt; " />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0 " />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="From: Lady Peggy Morrison," />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="&quot;From: Lady Peggy Morrison,&quot; &lt;jenni@reedtribe.org&gt; When my late husband was alive he deposited the sum of 20  Million (20Mi=" />
<meta name="Author" content="From: Lady Peggy Morrison, &lt;jenni@reedtribe.org&gt;" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-3443" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="From: Lady Peggy Morrison, &lt;jenni@reedtribe.org&gt;" />
<title>From: Lady Peggy Morrison,</title>
</head>
<body><p>From: Lady Peggy Morrison,
4 Old Church Street, Chelsea, SW3, England.

Here writes  Lady Peggy Morrison, suffering from cancerous ailment. I  am
married to Engineer Richard Morrison an Englishman who is dead. My  husband
was into private practice all his life before his death.  Our life together
as man and wife lasted for three decades without  child. My husband died
after aprotracted illness. My husband and  I made a vow to uplift the down-trodden
andthe less-privileged  individuals as he had passion for persons who can
not help  themselves due to physical disability or financial predicament.
I can adduce this to the fact that he needed a Child from this  relationship,which
never came.

 When my late husband was alive he deposited the sum of 20  Million (20Million
Great Britain Pounds Sterling which were  derived from his vast estates
a nd investment in capital market  with his bank here in UK. Presently,
this money is still with the  Bank.  Recently, my Doctor told me that I
have limited days to live  due to the cancerous problems I am suffering
from.

Though what bothers me most is the stroke that I have in addition  to the
cancer. With this hard reality that has befallen my family,  and me I have
decided to donate this fund to you and want you to  use this gift which
comes from my husbands effortto fund the  upkeep of widows, widowers, orphans,
destitute, the down-trodden,physically challenged children, barren-women
and persons who prove  to be genuinely handicapped financially.

It is often said that blessed is the hand that giveth. I took this  decision
because I do not have any child that will inherit this  money and my husband
relatives are bourgeois and very wealthy  persons and I do not want my husbands
hard earned money to be  misused or invested into ill perceived ventures.
I do not want a  situation where this money will be used in an ungodly manner,hence
the reason for taking this bold decision. I am not afraid of  death henceI
know where I am going. I know that I am going to be with the Almighty  when
Ieventually pass on. The Almighty will  fight my case and I shall hold my
peace.

I do not need any  telephone communication in this regard due to my
deteriorating  health and because of the presence of my husbands relatives
around me. I do not want them to know about this development. With God all
things are possible.

As soon as I receive your reply I shall give you the contact of  the bank
in UK. I will also issue you a Letter of Authority that  will empower you
as the original beneficiary of this fund via my Lawyer. My  happiness is
that I lived a life worthy of emulation. Please  always be prayerful all
t hrough your life. Please assure me that  you will act just as I have stated
herein. Hope to hear from you  soon and God bless you and members of your
family.you can contact me through my private email address:

Lady Peggy Morrison.
ladypeggymorrisonoffice14@yahoo.com.hk
4 Old Church Street, Chelsea, SW3, England.







</p>

</body></html>