<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="very confidential!!" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="Chen Jiang &lt;chenjiang022@yahoo.com.hk&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="Chen Jiang &lt;chenjiang022@yahoo.com.hk&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2007-03-14T22:12:17Z" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="chenjiang022@yahoo.com.hk" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/html;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-disposition" content="inline" />
<meta name="MboxParser-reply-to" content="chenjiang022@yahoo.com.hk" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-uidl" content="1173910337224902464" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="very confidential!!" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Reply-To" content="chenjiang022@yahoo.com.hk" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.3" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Disposition" content="inline" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Origin" content="81.199.173.50" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="binary" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;200703142212.l2EMCHw1022492@ps2.hostbasket.com&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="Chen Jiang &lt;chenjiang022@yahoo.com.hk&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="Chen Jiang &lt;chenjiang022@yahoo.com.hk&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Uidl" content="1173910337224902464" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/html;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="Chen Jiang &lt;chenjiang022@yahoo.com.hk&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="Chen Jiang &lt;chenjiang022@yahoo.com.hk&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2007-03-14T22:12:17Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Mime-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.3" />
<meta name="format" content="text/html;" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2007-03-14T22:12:17Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="binary" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;apache@ps2.hostbasket.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-mailer" content="AtMail Lite 3.43 - http://webbasedemail.com/" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Wed Mar 14 13:19:20 2007" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-origin" content="81.199.173.50" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;apache@ps2.hostbasket.com&gt; for the transfer.A bank account in &lt;BR&gt;any part of the world that you will provide will then facilitate the &lt;BR&gt;transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money &lt;BR&gt;will be paid into your &lt;BR&gt;account for us to share in the ratio of 50% for me and 50% for you. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will &lt;BR&gt;be done by the attorney and my position as the Branch Manager &lt;BR&gt;guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are &lt;BR&gt;interested, please reply immediately via the private email address &lt;BR&gt;chenjiang022@yahoo.com.hkUpon your response, I shall then provide you &lt;BR&gt;with more details and &lt;BR&gt;relevantdocuments that will help you understand the transaction. Please &lt;BR&gt;send me your confidential telephone and fax numbers for easy &lt;BR&gt;communication. &lt;BR&gt;Please observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this &lt;BR&gt;transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall &lt;BR&gt;require you!" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-Id" content="&lt;200703142212.l2EMCHw1022492@ps2.hostbasket.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="Chen Jiang" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="Chen Jiang &lt;chenjiang022@yahoo.com.hk&gt;" />
<meta name="Author" content="Chen Jiang &lt;chenjiang022@yahoo.com.hk&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Mailer" content="AtMail Lite 3.43 - http://webbasedemail.com/" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-3563" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="Chen Jiang &lt;chenjiang022@yahoo.com.hk&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;200703142212.l2EMCHw1022492@ps2.hostbasket.com&gt;" />
<title>very confidential!!</title>
</head>
<body>Good Day, 

I am Mr. Chen Jiang, Bank Manager of a Bank in China.I have an urgent 
and very confidential business proposition for you.On November 6, 2001, 
a British Oil consultant/contractor with the Chinese Solid Minerals 
Corporation, Made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar 
months, valued at US$30,000,000.00 (Thirty Million United States 
Dollars) in my branch.Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to 
his forwarding address but got no reply. 

After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his 
contract employers, the Chinese Solid Minerals Corporation that he died 
from an automobile accident. On further investigation, I found out that 
he died without making a WILL, and all attempts to trace his next of 
kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and 
discovered that he did not declare any kin or relations in all his 
official documents, including his Bank Depos!
it paperwork 
in my Bank. This sum of US$30,000,000.00 is still sitting in my Bank 
and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end 
of each year. 

No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to Laws ofRepublic 
of China, at the expiration of 6 (six) years, the money will revert to 
the ownership of the Chinese Government if nobody applies to claim the 
fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner 
to stand in as the next of kin to the man so that the fruits of this 
old man's 
labor will not get into the hands of some corrupt government 
officials.This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your 
full names and address so that the attorney will prepare the necessary 
documents and affidavits that will put you in place as the next of kin. 

shall employ the services of an attorney for drafting and authorization 
of the WILL and to obtain the necessary doc!
uments and letter of 
probate/administration in your favor!
 for the transfer.A bank account in 
any part of the world that you will provide will then facilitate the 
transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money 
will be paid into your 
account for us to share in the ratio of 50% for me and 50% for you. 

There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will 
be done by the attorney and my position as the Branch Manager 
guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are 
interested, please reply immediately via the private email address 
chenjiang022@yahoo.com.hkUpon your response, I shall then provide you 
with more details and 
relevantdocuments that will help you understand the transaction. Please 
send me your confidential telephone and fax numbers for easy 
communication. 
Please observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this 
transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall 
require you!
r assistance to invest my share in your country. 

Awaiting your urgent reply via my email address. 
chenjiang022@yahoo.com.hk 
Thanks and regards. 
Chen Jiang. 








</body></html>