<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="From: Mr. Maekal Mekha." />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="Mr. Maekal Mekha." />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="Maekal Mekha &lt;mekha_llcs@yahoo.dk&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="mekha_llcs@yahoo.dk" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2007-04-15T07:41:22Z" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="R@S of the Security Company in London,United Kingdom. I will also issue you =" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="R@S" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="R@S of the Security Company in London,United Kingdom. I will also issue you =" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="MboxParser-reply-to" content="mekha_llcs@yahoo.dk" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="From: Mr. Maekal Mekha." />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Reply-To" content="mekha_llcs@yahoo.dk" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.3" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;200704150741.l3F7fMrv002440@relay.dotsterhost.com&gt; disturbs me most is my stroke.=20" />
<meta name="creator" content="Mr. Maekal Mekha." />
<meta name="creator" content="Maekal Mekha &lt;mekha_llcs@yahoo.dk&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-sender-id" content="v2543 As soon as I receive your reply I shall give you the contact information=" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="Mr. Maekal Mekha." />
<meta name="meta:author" content="Maekal Mekha &lt;mekha_llcs@yahoo.dk&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2007-04-15T07:41:22Z" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-sieve" content="CMU Sieve 2.3 of March in the year 2007." />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2007-04-15T07:41:22Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;sendmail-proxy@relay.dotsterhost.com&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Sender-ID" content="v2543" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Sun Apr 15 03:40:36 2007" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;sendmail-proxy@relay.dotsterhost.com&gt; Let me start by introducing myself. I am  Mr. Maekal Mekha, a Baghda=" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-Id" content="&lt;200704150741.l3F7fMrv002440@relay.dotsterhost.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="Maekal Mekha" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="Mr. Maekal Mekha." />
<meta name="Author" content="Maekal Mekha &lt;mekha_llcs@yahoo.dk&gt;" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-3641" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="Maekal Mekha &lt;mekha_llcs@yahoo.dk&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;200704150741.l3F7fMrv002440@relay.dotsterhost.com&gt; disturbs me most is my stroke.=20" />
<title>From: Mr. Maekal Mekha.</title>
</head>
<body><p>From: Mr. Maekal Mekha.
17 Copse Hill,Baghdad
Iraq
 
My Dear Beloved,

     Let me start by introducing myself. I am  Mr. Maekal Mekha, a Baghdad Citizen, Iraq, a Mechant as an occupation. I have a obscured business suggestion for you. I am a brother to Dr.Gerald Mekha,who worked with 
Iraq Judicial Commission , Iraq, for over a decade before he died on 20th of March in the year 2007.

He died after a brief  illness that lasted for two weeks. Before his death he made a vow to use his wealth for the down trodden and the less privileged in the society. When my brother was alive he deposited the sum of £250 Million Pounds (Two Hundred and Fifty Million Pounds) with one United Kingdom Security Company in London.

This funds are still with the Security Company for the past 6 years now,the funds are locked in two metallic trunk boxes, deposited with these company, i am in a refugee camp here in Iraq, as a result of the war in 
Iraq this moment, am sorry am not too fine based on my health,though what disturbs me most is my stroke. 

Having known my condition and want to make sure i do my father's will, I have decided to donate this fund to an individual or company,that will utilize this money the way I am going to instruct herein. 

I want an individual or company that will use this to fund and provide succor to poor and indigent persons, orphanages, and widows and for propagating peace in the universe. I understand that blessed is the hand that giveth. I took this decision because I do not have any one that will inherit this money and my staying in the refugee camp, still don't know when i'll be granted the visa permit out of Iraq. I do not want a situation where this money will be used in an ungodly manner, hence the reason for taking this bold decision.

I do not need any telephone communication in this regard because of my uneasy access to the facility in the refugee camp here in Iraq. Also because of the presence of social security in the camp, I do not want them to know. With Allah all things are possible.

 As soon as I receive your reply I shall give you the contact information of the Security Company in London,United Kingdom. I will also issue you a letter of authority that will empower you as the original beneficiary of this fund. I want you to always pray for me.

My happiness is that I lived a life worthy of emulation. Whosoever that wants to serve the Almighty Allah must serve him with all his heart and mind and soul and also in truth. Please always be prayerful all through your life. Any delay in your reply will give me room in sourcing for an individual for this same purpose. Please assure me that you will act according to my specification herein. 

Hoping to hear from you. Thank you and may the Almighty Allah bless you.
Kindly send your email message to my mailbox :  mekha_llcs@yahoo.dk  , so i can contact you with more information 

Yours sincerely,
Mr. Maekal Mekha





</p>

</body></html>