<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="HOW ARE YOU TODAY?" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="&lt;fredkuma@freesurf.fr&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="fredkuma@freesurf.fr" />
<meta name="MboxParser-http" content="//www.freesurf.fr/adsl/" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="MboxParser-tel" content="229 08 69 05." />
<meta name="MboxParser-tel" content="229 08 69 05." />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2003-09-19T20:14:46Z" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="fredkuma@freesurf.fr" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="&lt;fredkuma@freesurf.fr&gt;" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="fredkuma@freesurf.fr" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=iso-8859-1" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="fredkuma@freesurf.fr" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Importance" content="Normal" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-ID" content="&lt;11607.81.199.80.151.1064002486.squirrel@arlette.freesurf.fr&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="HOW ARE YOU TODAY?" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="8bit" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;11607.81.199.80.151.1064002486.squirrel@arlette.freesurf.fr&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="&lt;fredkuma@freesurf.fr&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="fredkuma@freesurf.fr" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; charset=iso-8859-1" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="&lt;fredkuma@freesurf.fr&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="fredkuma@freesurf.fr" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2003-09-19T20:14:46Z" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=iso-8859-1" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2003-09-19T20:14:46Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="8bit" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;fredkuma@freesurf.fr&gt;	by bloodwork.mr.itd.UM (3.8u) with ESMTP id h8JJqg221842; Fri, 19 Sep 2003 15:52:43 -0400 (EDT)        Fri, 19 Sep 2003 22:14:46 +0200 (CEST)" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-mailer" content="SquirrelMail (version 1.2.5)" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-priority" content="3" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Priority" content="3" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-MSMail-Priority" content="Normal" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Fri Sep 19 15:52:49 2003" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;fredkuma@freesurf.fr&gt; by bloodwork.mr.itd.UM (3.8u) with ESMTP id h8JJqg221842; Fri, 19 Sep 2003 15:52:43 -0400 (EDT) Fri, 19 Sep 2003 22:14:46 +0200 (CEST)" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="&lt;fredkuma@freesurf.fr&gt;" />
<meta name="Author" content="fredkuma@freesurf.fr" />
<meta name="MboxParser-importance" content="Normal" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Mailer" content="SquirrelMail (version 1.2.5)" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-msmail-priority" content="Normal" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-420" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="fredkuma@freesurf.fr" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;11607.81.199.80.151.1064002486.squirrel@arlette.freesurf.fr&gt;" />
<title>HOW ARE YOU TODAY?</title>
</head>
<body><p>FROM MR FRED KUMA.
REPUBLIC OF BENIN.
WEST AFRICA.
TEL:229 08 69 05.


Dear Friend,

I am MR FRED KUMA, the director in charge of auditing and accounting
section of Continental Trust Bank cotonou republic of benin in west Africa
with due respect and regard. I have decided to contact you on a business
transaction that will be very beneficial to both of  us at the end of the
transaction .

During our investigation and auditing in this bank,my department came
across a very huge sum of money belonging to a deceased person who died in
a plane crash on the 26th December 1998 on airline transafrik
International with aircraft Lockheed L-100-30 at location Vila Nova,Angola
with registration number S9-CAO and since his untimely death the funds has
been dormant in his account with this Bank without any claim of the fund in
our custody either from his family or relation before our discovery to this
development.

Although personally, I keep this information secret within myself and
partners to enable the whole plans and idea be Profitable and
successful during the time of execution. The said amount was US$24.1M
(Twenty Four million One Hundred Thousand united states dollars).

As it may interest you to know, I got your impressive information
through my a friends who works with the Ministry of Information here in
Cotonou-Benin. It is him who recommended your person to me to be viable and
capable to champion a business of such magnitude without any problem.
Meanwhile all the whole arrangement to put claim over this fund as the
bonafide next of kin to the deceased,get the required approval and transfer
this money to a foreign account has been put in place and directives and
needed information will be relayed to you as soon as you indicate your
interest and willingness to assist us and also benefit yourself to this
great business opportunity.

In fact I could have done this deal alone but because of my position in
this country as a civil servant,we  are not allowed to operate a foreign
account and would eventually raise an eye brow on my side during the time
of transfer because I work in this bank. This is the actual reason why it
will require a second party or fellow who will forward claims as the next
of kin to the Bank and also present a foreign account where he will need
the money to be re-transferred into on his request as it may be after due
verification and clarification by the correspondent branch of the bank
where the whole money will be remitted from to your own designated bank
account.

May I at this point emphasize that this transaction is 100% risk free as I
have made arrangements for a successful arrangement as an insider of the
bank before contacting you.  On smooth conclusion of this transaction, you
will be entitled to 30% of the total sum as gratification, while 10% will
be set aside to take care of expenses that may arise during the time of
transfer and also telephone bills, while 60% will be for me and my partners.

Please, you have been adviced to keep this a top secret as we are still in
service and intend to retire from service after we conclude this deal with
you.

I will be monitoring the whole situation here in this bank until you
confirm the money in your account and ask us to come down to your country
for subsequent sharing of the fund according to percentages previously
indicated and further investment, either in your country or any country you
advice us to invest in.

All other necessary information will be sent to you on your acceptance to
champion this transaction with me.

I suggest you get back to me as soon as possible on my personal mobile
phone 229 08 69 05 stating your wish in this deal.

Yours faithfully,

DR FRED KUMA

TEL:229 08 69 05.
ALTERNATIVE EMAIL:
efftee2002@eudoramail.com



----------------------------------------------------------------
Ce service de mailing vous est offert par http://www.freesurf.fr.
FreeSurf, votre acces ADSL a partir de 29 euros/mois
http://www.freesurf.fr/adsl/



</p>

</body></html>