<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="BUSINESS RELATIONSHIP" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="errol_marshall2@albawaba.com BUSINESS PROPOSAL/RELATIONSHIP" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="errol_marshall2@albawaba.com" />
<meta name="MboxParser-tel" content="27 -73-2665538 or 27-83-5828584" />
<meta name="MboxParser-tel" content="27 -73-2665538 or 27-83-5828584" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="O MR. Errol Marshall" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2003-10-20T04:36:36Z" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="errol_marshall2@albawaba.com" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="errol_marshall2@albawaba.com In order to transfer out (USD 126 M) One hundred and twenty six million United States Dollars) from African Development Bank. I have the courage to ask you to look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable for this important business believing that you will never let me down either now or in future." />
<meta name="Message-To" content="errol_marshall2@albawaba.com" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=US-ASCII ATTN;" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="errol_marshall2@albawaba.com In order to transfer out (USD 126 M) One hundred and twenty six million United States Dollars) from African Development Bank. I have the courage to ask you to look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable for this important business believing that you will never let me down either now or in future." />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="O" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="BUSINESS RELATIONSHIP" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="7BIT AFFAIRES PROPOSAL/RELATIONSHIP" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;20031020044426.256E4C2A9@krusty.si.UM&gt; In order to transfer out (USD 126 M) One hundred and twenty six million United States Dollars) from African Development Bank. I have the courage to ask you to look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable for this important business believing that you will never let me down either now or in future." />
<meta name="creator" content="errol_marshall2@albawaba.com BUSINESS PROPOSAL/RELATIONSHIP" />
<meta name="creator" content="errol_marshall2@albawaba.com" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; charset=US-ASCII" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="errol_marshall2@albawaba.com BUSINESS PROPOSAL/RELATIONSHIP" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="errol_marshall2@albawaba.com" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2003-10-20T04:36:36Z" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=US-ASCII ATTN;" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2003-10-20T04:36:36Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="7BIT" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;errol_marshall2@albawaba.com&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-mailer" content="DMailer for Windows V1.1 FRENCH" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Mon Oct 20 00:44:12 2003" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;errol_marshall2@albawaba.com&gt; NO 180 COMMISSIONER STREET," />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-Id" content="&lt;20031020044426.256E4C2A9@krusty.si.UM&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0 NO 180 COMMISSIONER STREET," />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="BUSINESS PROPOSAL/RELATIONSHIP" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="errol_marshall2@albawaba.com BUSINESS PROPOSAL/RELATIONSHIP" />
<meta name="Author" content="errol_marshall2@albawaba.com" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Mailer" content="DMailer for Windows V1.1" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-486" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="errol_marshall2@albawaba.com" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;20031020044426.256E4C2A9@krusty.si.UM&gt; In order to transfer out (USD 126 M) One hundred and twenty six million United States Dollars) from African Development Bank. I have the courage to ask you to look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable for this important business believing that you will never let me down either now or in future." />
<title>BUSINESS RELATIONSHIP</title>
</head>
<body><p>FROM THE DESK OF E.MARSHALL
 NO 180 COMMISSIONER STREET, 
JOHANNESBURG, SOUTH AFRICA.
Tel: 27 -73-2665538 or 27-83-5828584
 ATTN; 
                             BUSINESS PROPOSAL/RELATIONSHIP
 In order to transfer out (USD 126 M) One hundred and twenty six million United States Dollars) from African Development Bank. I have the courage to ask you to look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable for this important business believing that you will never let me down either now or in future. 

I am Mr. Errol Marshall, the Chief auditor of African Development Bank (ADB). There is an account opened in this bank in 1990 and since 1995 nobody has operated on this account again.After going through some old files in the records, I discovered that if I do not remit this money out urgently it would be forfeited for nothing. The owner of this account is Mr.Smith B.Andreas a foreigner, and a miner at kruger gold co,a geologist by profession and he died since 1994. No other person knows about this account or any thing concerning it, the account has no other beneficiary and my investigation proved to me as well that this company does not know anything about this account and the amount involved is (USD $126M) One hundred and twenty six million United States Dollars. I want to first transfer US$26( twenty six million United States Dollars) from this money into a safe foreigners account abroad before the rest, but I don't know any foreigner.

I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money cannot be approved to a local bank here, but can only be approved to any foreign account because the money is in us dollars and the former owner of the account is Mr. Smith B.Andreas he is a foreigner too. I know that this message will come to you as a surprise as we don't know ourselves before. We will sign an agreement, but be sure that it is real and a genuine business. I only got your contact address from my secretary who operates computer, with believe in God that you will never let me down in this business. You are the only person that I have contacted in this business, so please reply urgently so that I will inform you the next step to take immediately. 

Send also your private telephone and fax number including the full details of the account to be used for the deposit. I want us to meet face to face or sign a binding agreement to bind us together so that you can receive this money into a foreign account or any account of your choice where the fund will be safe. And I will fly to your country for withdrawal and sharing and other investments. I am contacting you because of the need to involve a foreigner with foreign account and foreign beneficiary. I need your full co-peration to make this work fine because the management is ready to approve this payment to any foreigner, who has correct information of this account, which I will give to you immediately, if you are able and with capability to handle such amount in strict confidence and trust according to my instructions and advice for our mutual benefit because this opportunity will never come again in my life. I need truthful person in this business because I don't want to make mistake I need you strong assurance and trust. With my position now in the office I can transfer this money to any foreigner's reliable account, which you can provide with assurance that this money will be intact pending my physical arrival in your country for sharing. I will destroy all documents of transaction immediately we receive this money leaving no trace to any place. You can also come to discuss with me face to face after which I will make this remittance in your presence and two of us will fly to your country at least two days ahead of the money going into the account. 

I will apply for annual leave to get visa immediately I hear from you that you are ready to act and receive this fund in your account. I will use my position and influence to effect legal approvals and onward transfer of this money to your account with appropriate clearance forms of the ministries and foreign exchange departments. At the conclusion of this business, you will be given 35% of the total amount, 60% will be for me, while 5% will be for expenses both parties might have incurred during the process of transferring. I look forward to your earliest reply. 

Best regards
 MR. Errol Marshall
                    				FRENCH
DU BUREAU D'E.MARSHALL
 NO 180 COMMISSIONER STREET, 
JOHANNESBURG, SOUTH AFRICA.
Tel: 27 -73-2665538 or 27-83-5828584
 ATTN; 
        				AFFAIRES PROPOSAL/RELATIONSHIP

 In order to transfer out (USD 126 M) One hundred and twenty six million United States Dollars) from African Development Bank. I have the courage to ask you to look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable for this important business believing that you will never let me down either now or in future. 

Je suis M. Errol Marshall, l'auditeur en chef de la banque de développement africaine (ADB). Il y a un compte ouvert à cette banque en 1990 et depuis 1995 où personne n'a opéré ce compte again.After passant par quelques vieux dossiers dans les disques, j'a découvert que si je ne remets pas cet argent hors de instamment il serait renoncé pour rien. Le propriétaire de ce compte est Mr.Smith B.Andreas un Étranger, et un mineur à l'or Co de kruger, à un géologue par profession et à lui sont morts depuis 1994. Aucune autre personne ne sait ce compte ou n'importe quelle chose au sujet d'elle, le compte n'a aucun autre bénéficiaire et ma recherche montré aussi bien s à moi que cette compagnie ne sait pas que n'importe quoi au sujet de ce compte et de la quantité impliquée est (USD $126M) cent vingt six millions de dollars des Etats-Unis. Je veux au premier transfert USS26(vingt six millions de dollars des Etats-Unis) de cet argent dans un coffre-fort les Étrangers rendent compte à l'étranger avant le repos, mais je ne connais aucun Étranger.
Je vous contacte seulement en tant qu'Étranger parce que cet argent ne peut pas être approuvé à une banque locale ici, mais peux seulement être approuvé à n'importe quel compte étranger parce que l'argent est dans nous des dollars et l'ancien propriétaire du compte est M. Smith B.Andreas qu'il est un Étranger aussi. Je sais que ce message viendra à vous car une surprise car nous ne nous connaissons pas avant. Nous signerons l'accord, mais soit sûr que c'est vrai et des affaires véritables. J'ai seulement obtenu votre adresse de contact de mon secrétaire qui actionne l'ordinateur, avec crois en Dieu que vous ne m'avez jamais laissé vers le bas dans ces affaires. Vous êtes la seule personne que j'ai contactée dans ces affaires, satisfaites ainsi la réponse instamment de sorte que je vous informe la prochaine étape pour prendre immédiatement.
Envoyez également votre numéro de fax privé de téléphone et comprenant les détails complets du compte à employer pour le dépôt. Je veux que nous se réunissent face à face ou signent un accord obligatoire de nous lier ensemble de sorte que vous puissiez recevoir cet argent en compte étranger ou n'importe quel compte de votre choix où les fonds seront sûrs. Et je volerai à votre pays pour le retrait et partage et autre investissements. Je vous contacte en raison de la nécessité de faire participer un Étranger du compte étranger et le bénéficiaire étranger. J'ai besoin de votre pleine Co-peration pour faire ce travail très bien parce que la gestion est prête à approuver ce paiement à n'importe quel Étranger, qui a l'information correcte de ce compte, que qui je vous donnerai immédiatement, si vous pouvez en mesure et avec des possibilités manipuler une telle quantité la confiance et en la confiance strictes selon mes instructions et conseil pour notre avantage mutuel parce que cette occasion ne viendra encore jamais dans ma vie. J'ai besoin de personne véridique dans ces affaires parce que je ne veux pas faire l'erreur que j'ai besoin de vous assurance et confiance fortes. Avec ma position maintenant dans le bureau je peux virer cet argent sur le compte fiable de n'importe quel Étranger, qui vous pouvez fournir l'assurance à que cet argent sera intact en attendant ma arrivée physique dans votre pays pour le partage. Je détruirai tous les documents de transaction immédiatement que nous recevons cet argent ne laissant aucune trace à n'importe quel endroit. Vous pouvez également venir pour discuter avec moi face à face après quoi je ferai cette remise en votre présence et deux de nous voleront à votre pays au moins pendant deux jours en avant de l'argent entrant en compte.
Je solliciterai le congé annuel pour obtenir le visa immédiatement que je reçois des nouvelles vous que vous êtes prêt à agir et à recevoir ces fonds dans votre compte. J'emploierai ma position et influence pour effectuer des approbations légales et le transfert en avant de cet argent à votre compte avec les formes appropriées de dégagement des ministères et des départements de devises étrangères. À la conclusion de ces affaires, vous soyez donné 35% du montant total, 60% sera pour moi, alors que 5% sera pour des dépenses que les deux parties pourraient avoir encourues pendant le processus du transfert. J'attends avec intérêt votre première réponse.
Les meilleurs souvenirs
 MR. Errol Marshall



</p>

</body></html>