<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="&quot;ATTN. QUICK SUPPORT&quot;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2003-11-06T09:34:12Z" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=us-ascii" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="bluemariam@katamail.com email;palmgroovechambers@winningteam.com)" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="bluemariam@katamail.com" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-wmSenderIP" content="192.116.79.158" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="bluemariam@katamail.com email;palmgroovechambers@winningteam.com)" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="&quot;ATTN. QUICK SUPPORT&quot;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-ID" content="&lt;192.116.79.158+W8UdiORV0p7iiUElQ@all-1.inet.it&gt;" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="8bit" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;192.116.79.158+W8UdiORV0p7iiUElQ@all-1.inet.it&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; charset=us-ascii" />
<meta name="MboxParser-disclaimer" content="This e-mail message and any attachments are" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2003-11-06T09:34:12Z" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=us-ascii" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2003-11-06T09:34:12Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="8bit" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-wmsenderip" content="192.116.79.158" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;bluemariam@katamail.com&gt;	by magnumforce.mr.itd.UM (3.8u) with ESMTP id hA69dPZ24301	for &lt;R@M&gt;; Thu, 6 Nov 2003 04:39:25 -0500 (EST)" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-mailer" content="Katamail" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Thu Nov  6 04:39:25 2003" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;bluemariam@katamail.com&gt; by magnumforce.mr.itd.UM (3.8u) with ESMTP id hA69dPZ24301 for &lt;R@M&gt;; Thu, 6 Nov 2003 04:39:25 -0500 (EST) details." />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Mailer" content="Katamail" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-538" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;192.116.79.158+W8UdiORV0p7iiUElQ@all-1.inet.it&gt;" />
<title>"ATTN. QUICK SUPPORT"</title>
</head>
<body><p>CONTACT ME THROUGH MY ATTORNEYS FAX; 234-1-7591936 OR EMAIL

Compliments of the day to you!

I am Mrs. Mariam Abacha widow of the late General Sanni Abacha
former Nigerian Military President who died on active Government
service on june 8, 1998.

I got your contact from the Internet and I do believe you can
help me.

I am contacting you due to the present situation as regards the
undemocratic manner the present administration in my country
(Nigeria) is taking all that belongs to us You may be aware
that this is the usual attitude of leaders especially in Africa
when there is a change of Government. The present Government of
General Olusegun Obasanjo is currently in a face off with my
family in his bid to recover all our money because my Husband is
dead.

They have brought up charges of corrupt enrichmemnt against us.
Unfortunately, he is currently facing same from the National
Assembly right now. I pray he does not get an Impeachment The
law they made is yet another smear campaign aimed mainly to
frustrate, humiliate, dismember and widen the scope of hatred for
my family. A personal vendetta by President Obasanjo who was
jailed by my husband's Government for plotting a coup d 'etat
against his administration in 1995.


This highly calculated attempt by this administration plus some
Western Banks through bi-lateral relationship has taken away from
us a whopping amount in Switzerland and Bank accounts around the
World. This rampaging of our Bank accounts abroad have yielded to
the barbaric pressure and just few months ago we were squized
out of another US$395m because the accounts bear our names. This
assertions can be ascertained independently if you wish to
confirm this from a leading newspaper in Nigeria (This Day Newspapers) from
their website at www.thisdayonline.com from the archives section in the
March 10,2001, January 26,2002 and March 18, 2002 editions.

This pressure is taking a great toll on my family and all we ever
owe. You may be aware that my surviving eldest son (Mohammed),
was undully detained without trial untill thursday 11TH of July
2002 one year now that the Supreme Court of Nigeria Ordered his
release and cleared him of any wrong doing as he has been
languishing in prison for the past three and half years. It was on Monday
23RD September last year that he was finally released to us.

Please we wish to solicit your cooperation as a foreigner to help
us receive some family property / (Money) Deposited with a
Security company which is our only hope / source of livelihood
for now. This is a call for you to help receive this money and
put the money into good investments since we are barred from
leaving the Country for now.

According to my estimation in Western Europe and America alone we
still have over US$70M in cash with Security Companies that we
intend to put in your care by getting a trusted foreigner to
handle money for the purpose of investment and safekeeping abroad.

Please Note that you will be expected to deal directly with the
security company with the information and LEGAL POWER we shall
give you to handle the entire transaction. There is demurrage
accrued over time payable to Security Company to enable
collection of the Consignment, since the Deposit we made at the
time of Deposit has since expired. You must also know that CONSIGNMENT WAS
DEPOSITED AS FAMILY TREASURES, ACTUAL CONTENT ON CONSIGNMENT WAS NOT DECLARED
TO SECURITY COMPANY AT THE TIME OF DEPOSIT TO SAFE GUARD IT. If you can
do this, contact my ATTORNEY, BARRISTER ALI KOLOMA Fax; 234-1-7591936 as
you will be well REWARDED. This is however subject to our negotiation and
agreement.

You can contact me ONLY via our family Attorney, Barrister Ali
Koloma, BY email: palmgroovechambers@winningteam.com for security reason and further
 details.

Endeavor to keep this highly confidential. In your response
include your private telephone / fax numbers for easy
communications with him.

My kind regards,

Mrs. Mariam Abacha
(PLEASE REPLY ONLY TO; my Attorneys FAX NUMBER; 234-1-7591936, OR
 email;palmgroovechambers@winningteam.com)

DISCLAIMER:This e-mail message and any attachments are
confidential and may be privileged or otherwise protected by
legal rules, and for use by the addressee only. If the message is
received by anyone other than the addressee, please return the
message to the sender and delete it and any attachments from your
computer without copying it or disclosing its contents to anyone.
Whilst all reasonable care has been taken to avoid the
transmission of viruses, no responsibility is accepted in this
regard and the recipient should scan and carry out such other
checks as it considers appropriate.




</p>

</body></html>