<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="KALADA HART" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="kaladah@epatra.com " />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="kaladah@epatra.com" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2003-11-25T06:37:29Z" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="kaladah@epatra.com" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="webmaster@aclweb.org" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="webmaster@aclweb.org" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain;" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="webmaster@aclweb.org" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="MboxParser-reply-to" content="kaladah@epatra.com" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="KALADA HART" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Reply-To" content="kaladah@epatra.com" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;200311250637.hAP6bOU7002695@cs.CU&gt; made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months," />
<meta name="creator" content="kaladah@epatra.com " />
<meta name="creator" content="kaladah@epatra.com" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain;	charset=&quot;US-ASCII&quot;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Library" content="Indy 9.0.3-B" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="kaladah@epatra.com " />
<meta name="meta:author" content="kaladah@epatra.com" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2003-11-25T06:37:29Z" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain;" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2003-11-25T06:37:29Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;R@O&gt;	for &lt;R@O&gt;; Tue, 25 Nov 2003 01:37:32 -0500 (EST)" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-mailer" content="Foxmail" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-priority" content="3" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Priority" content="3" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Tue Nov 25 01:37:44 2003" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;R@O&gt; for &lt;R@O&gt;; Tue, 25 Nov 2003 01:37:32 -0500 (EST) charset=&quot;US-ASCII&quot;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-Id" content="&lt;200311250637.hAP6bOU7002695@cs.CU&gt;" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="kaladah@epatra.com " />
<meta name="Author" content="kaladah@epatra.com" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Mailer" content="Foxmail" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-568" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="kaladah@epatra.com" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-library" content="Indy 9.0.3-B" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;200311250637.hAP6bOU7002695@cs.CU&gt; made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months," />
<title>KALADA HART</title>
</head>
<body><p>MR. KALADA HART
ORIENT BANK (NIG.) LTD.
IDUMOTA BRANCH 
LAGOS. - NIGERIA.




Dear Sir,

I am Mr Kalada Hart, Bank Manager of Orient Bank of Nigeria,
Lagos Branch. I have an urgent and very confidential business 
proposition for you.

On September 6, 1997, a Canadian Oil consultant/contractor with 
the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation, Mr. Jerry Sheldon
 made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months, 
valued at US$25,000,000.00 (Twenty- five Million Dollars) in my branch. 
Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to his forwarding 
address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and 
finally we discovered from his contract employers, the Nigerian 
National Petroleum Corporation that Mr. Jerry Sheldon died from 
an automobile accident. On further investigation, I found out that 
he died without making a WILL, and all attempts to trace his next 
of kin was fruitless.

I therefore made further investigation and discovered that 
Mr. Jerry Sheldon did not declare any kin or relations in all his 
official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. 
This sum of US$25,000,000.00 is still sitting in my Bank and the 
interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each 
year. No one has ever come forward to claim it. According to Nigerian 
Law, at the expiration of 5 (five) years, the money will revert to the 
ownership of the Nigerian Government if nobody applies to claim the fund.

Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you to stand in as the 
next of kin to Mr. Jerry Sheldon so that the fruits of this old man's 
labor will not get into the hands of some corrupt government official
s. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full 
names and address so that the Attorney will prepare the necessary 
documents and affidavits which will put you in place as the next of kin. 
We shall employ the service of two Attorney for drafting and notarization 
of the WILL and to obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate/
administration in your favor for the transfer. 
A bank account in any part of the world which you will provide will then 
facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. 
The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 
70% for me and 30% for you.

There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be 
done by the Attorney and my position as the Branch Manager guaranttees 
the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, 
please reply immediately via the private email address 
below. Upon your response, I shall then provide you with more details 
and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction.

Please observe utmost confidentiality, and be rest assured that this 
transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall 
require your assistance to invest my share in your country.

Awaiting your urgent reply via my email.

Thanks and regards.

Mr.Kalada Hart

Confidiential Email Address you should respond to: kaladah@yahoo.com




 


</p>

</body></html>