<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="FROM JOHN CARLOS" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="&quot;john carlos&quot; &lt;johncarlos26@webmail.co.za&gt; " />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="john carlos &lt;johncarlos26@webmail.co.za&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2004-04-08T09:51:15Z" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="johncarlos26@webmail.co.za" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="johncarlos26@webmail.co.za" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="johncarlos26@webmail.co.za" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;ISO-8859-1&quot;" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="johncarlos26@webmail.co.za" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="FROM JOHN CARLOS" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-ID" content="&lt;web-279767916@mail01.infosat.net&gt;" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="8bit" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;web-279767916@mail01.infosat.net&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="&quot;john carlos&quot; &lt;johncarlos26@webmail.co.za&gt; " />
<meta name="creator" content="john carlos &lt;johncarlos26@webmail.co.za&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;ISO-8859-1&quot;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="&quot;john carlos&quot; &lt;johncarlos26@webmail.co.za&gt; " />
<meta name="meta:author" content="john carlos &lt;johncarlos26@webmail.co.za&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2004-04-08T09:51:15Z" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;ISO-8859-1&quot;" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2004-04-08T09:51:15Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="8bit" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-mailer" content="CommuniGate Pro WebUser Interface v.4.1.8" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Thu Apr  8 05:51:56 2004" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="john carlos" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="&quot;john carlos&quot; &lt;johncarlos26@webmail.co.za&gt; " />
<meta name="Author" content="john carlos &lt;johncarlos26@webmail.co.za&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Mailer" content="CommuniGate Pro WebUser Interface v.4.1.8" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-790" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="john carlos &lt;johncarlos26@webmail.co.za&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;web-279767916@mail01.infosat.net&gt;" />
<title>FROM JOHN CARLOS</title>
</head>
<body><p>FROM: JOHN CARLOS
TEL-27 83 342 4228
CAPE TOWN, SOUTHAFRICA.
                                            
Dear sir/madam

              ASSISTANT AND INVESTMENT

You may be surprise to receive this letter from me since
you don't know me personally. I am the son of Dr. David
Carlos who was recently murdered in the land dispute in
Zimbabwe. I got your contact through Network on line in my
search for a reliable and reputable person to handle a very

Confidential transaction which involves a transfer of fund
to a foreign account and I decided to write you, My Late
Father was among the few Black Zimbabwean Rich Farmers
murdered in Cold Blood by the agents of the ruling
government of President Robert Mugabe for his alleged
support and sympathy for the Zimbabwean opposition party
controlled by the white minority. 

Before his death he had taken to Johannesburg - South
Africa to deposit the sum of US$ 18.5 Million (Eighteen
Million Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) with
Security and Finance Company as if he foresaw the looming
danger in Zimbabwe. The money was deposited in a Box as 
Valuables to avoid much demurrage from the Security
Company. This money was embarked from the purchase of New
Machinery and Chemical for Farms and the establishment of
new farms in Lesotho and Swaziland. 

This land problem arose when President Robert Mugabe
introduced a new land act that wholly affected the Rich
White Farmers and some few blacks vehemently condemned the
"Modus Operandi" adopted by the government.  This resulted
to rampant killing and mob action by the war veterans and
some political thugs. Precisely, More than thirty-one (31)
people have so far been killed. Heads of governments from
the west, especially Britain and United States of America
have voiced their condemnation of Mugabe's plan.
Subsequently, South African Development Community (S.A.D.C)
has continuously supported Mugabe's new land act, it is
against this background that I and my family who are
currently residing in South Africa have decided  to
transfer my Father's money into a Foreign Account. 

As the eldest son of my Father, I am saddled with the
responsibility of seeking a genuine foreign account where
this money could be transferred without the knowledge of my
government who are tactically freezing our family wealth
and South Africa's government seems to be playing along
with them. I am faced with the dilemma of investing this
money in South Africa for fear of encountering the same
experience in future since both countries have almost the
same political history. More so, the South African Foreign
Exchange policy does not allow such investment hence we are
seeking for an "ASYLUM".

As a businessperson whom I entrusted my future and that of
my family into his hands, I must let you know that this
transaction is 100% risk free and the nature of your
business does not necessarily matter. For your assistance,
we are offering you 30% of the total sum, 60% for Me and My
Family while 10% will be mapped out for any expenses we may
incurs during the course of this transaction. We wish to
invest our part of the money on commercial property based
on your advice.


Finally, all we demand from you is assurance that you will
not sit on this money when it finally gets to your personal
or company's account in your country. If this proposal is
acceptable by you, please confirm your interest via the
above TEL and or E-MAIL me.

Thanks and God Bless you.

Best Regards.
John Carlos











______________________________________________________________
Herbalife Independent Distributor http://www.healthiest.co.za

</p>

</body></html>