<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="PROFITABLE BUSINESS VENTURE FOR YOU AND I" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="&quot;Mrs. Monica Kofi&quot; &lt;monicakofi@voila.fr&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="Mrs. Monica Kofi &lt;monicakofi@voila.fr&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="O" />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="monicakofi@voila.fr" />
<meta name="dcterms:created" content="2004-05-15T19:06:53Z" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="R@M" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="R@M" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;us-ascii&quot;" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="R@M" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="O" />
<meta name="MboxParser-reply-to" content="monicakofi@voila.fr" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Reply-To" content="monicakofi@voila.fr" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="PROFITABLE BUSINESS VENTURE FOR YOU AND I" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;200405151906.i4FJ6qfb025648@granny.mr.itd.UM&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="&quot;Mrs. Monica Kofi&quot; &lt;monicakofi@voila.fr&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="Mrs. Monica Kofi &lt;monicakofi@voila.fr&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;us-ascii&quot;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="&quot;Mrs. Monica Kofi&quot; &lt;monicakofi@voila.fr&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="Mrs. Monica Kofi &lt;monicakofi@voila.fr&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2004-05-15T19:06:53Z" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;us-ascii&quot;" />
<meta name="Creation-Date" content="2004-05-15T19:06:53Z" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;monicakofi@voila.fr&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-x-mailer" content="Microsoft Outlook Express 5.00.2919.6900 DM" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Sat May 15 15:06:58 2004" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;monicakofi@voila.fr&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-Id" content="&lt;200405151906.i4FJ6qfb025648@granny.mr.itd.UM&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="Mrs. Monica Kofi" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="&quot;Mrs. Monica Kofi&quot; &lt;monicakofi@voila.fr&gt;" />
<meta name="Author" content="Mrs. Monica Kofi &lt;monicakofi@voila.fr&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:X-Mailer" content="Microsoft Outlook Express 5.00.2919.6900 DM" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-835" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="Mrs. Monica Kofi &lt;monicakofi@voila.fr&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;200405151906.i4FJ6qfb025648@granny.mr.itd.UM&gt;" />
<title>PROFITABLE BUSINESS VENTURE FOR YOU AND I</title>
</head>
<body><p>INTERNATIONAL COMMERCIAL BANK LTD. (ICB).
CIRCLE ACCRA BRANCH, ACCRA-GHANA.

Beloved One,

Sir,

Let me start by introducing myself. I am Mrs. Monica Kofi credit

officer of the International Commercial Bank Ltd. (ICB) I have a

concealed business suggestion for you. Before the U.S and Iraqi war our

client General. Ibrahim Moussa who was with the Iraqi forces and also

business man made a numbered fixed deposit for 18 calendar months, with

a value of (US$8,000,000.00) Eight Millions United State Dollars only

in my branch. Upon maturity several notice was sent to him, even during

the war early this year. Again after the war another notification was

sent and still no response came from him.

We later find out that the General and his family had been killed

during the war in bomb blast that hit their home. After further

investigation it was also discovered that Gen. Ibrahim Moussa did not

declare any next of kin in his official papers including the paper work

of his bank deposit. And he also confided in me the last time he was at

my office that no one except me knew of his deposit in my bank.

So, Twenty millions Five Hundred Thousand United State Dollars is still

lying in my bank and no one will ever come forward to claim it. What

bothers me most is that according to the to the laws of my country at

the expiration 3 years the funds will revert to the ownership of the

Ghana Government if nobody applies to claim the funds. Against this

backdrop, my suggestion to you is that I will like you as a foreigner

to stand as the next of kin to Gen. Ibrahim Moussa so that you will be

able to receive his funds.

WHAT IS TO BE DONE:

I want you to know that I have had everything planned out so that we

shall come out successful. I have contacted an attorney that will

prepare the necessary document that will back you up as the next of kin

to Gen. Ibrahim Moussa, all that is required from you at this stage is

for you to provide me with your Full Names and Address so that the

attorney can commence his job. After you have been made the next of

kin, the attorney will also fill in for claims on your behalf and

secure the necessary approval and letter of probate in your favor for

the move of the funds to an account that will be provided by you.

There is no risk involved at all in the matter as we are going adopt a

Legalized method and the attorney will prepare all the necessary

documents. Please endeavor to observe utmost discretion in all matters

concerning this issue. Once the funds have been transferred to your

nominated bank account we shall share in the ratio of 50% for me, 40%

for you and 10% for the Charity/Motherless babies Home. Should you be

interested please send me your private phone and fax numbers for easy

communication and I will provide you with more details of this

operation.

Your earliest response to this letter will be appreciated. You can as

well call me on this number for more clarifications: + 233-24-4026959

for more information. And easy communication.

Kind Regards,

Mrs. Monica Kofi.


</p>

</body></html>