<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="identifier" content="&lt;20040702071553.54280.qmail@web54008.mail.yahoo.com&gt; Land" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="subject" content="APPRECIATION!" />
<meta name="format" content="multipart/alternative; boundary=&quot;0-1183065902-1088752552=:51796&quot; importantly&lt;BR&gt;this money I intend to&lt;BR&gt;use for investment.&lt;BR&gt;I have two options for you. Firstly you can choose&lt;BR&gt;to have certain&lt;BR&gt;percentage of the money for nominating your account&lt;BR&gt;for this&lt;BR&gt;transaction. Or you can go into partnership with me&lt;BR&gt;for a proper&lt;BR&gt;profitable investment in your country. Whichever&lt;BR&gt;option you want, feel&lt;BR&gt;free to notify me. I have also mapped out 5% of this&lt;BR&gt;money for all kinds&lt;BR&gt;of expenses incured in the process of this&lt;BR&gt;transaction. If you do not&lt;BR&gt;prefer a partnership I am willing to give you 10% of&lt;BR&gt;the money while the&lt;BR&gt;remaining 85% will be for my investment in your&lt;BR&gt;country. Contact me with&lt;BR&gt;the E-mail address while I implore you to maintain&lt;BR&gt;the absolute secrecy&lt;BR&gt;required in this transaction. Thanks, God bless you.&lt;/DIV&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="RO &lt;hr size=1&gt;Do you Yahoo!?&lt;br&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="multipart/alternative; boundary=&quot;0-1183065902-1088752552=:51796&quot; importantly&lt;BR&gt;this money I intend to&lt;BR&gt;use for investment.&lt;BR&gt;I have two options for you. Firstly you can choose&lt;BR&gt;to have certain&lt;BR&gt;percentage of the money for nominating your account&lt;BR&gt;for this&lt;BR&gt;transaction. Or you can go into partnership with me&lt;BR&gt;for a proper&lt;BR&gt;profitable investment in your country. Whichever&lt;BR&gt;option you want, feel&lt;BR&gt;free to notify me. I have also mapped out 5% of this&lt;BR&gt;money for all kinds&lt;BR&gt;of expenses incured in the process of this&lt;BR&gt;transaction. If you do not&lt;BR&gt;prefer a partnership I am willing to give you 10% of&lt;BR&gt;the money while the&lt;BR&gt;remaining 85% will be for my investment in your&lt;BR&gt;country. Contact me with&lt;BR&gt;the E-mail address while I implore you to maintain&lt;BR&gt;the absolute secrecy&lt;BR&gt;required in this transaction. Thanks, God bless you.&lt;/DIV&gt;" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="prince_philip28@yahoo.com my" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="prince_philip28@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="MboxParser---0-1183065902-1088752552=" content="51796" />
<meta name="MboxParser---0-1183065902-1088752552=" content="51796" />
<meta name="MboxParser---0-1183065902-1088752552=" content="51796--" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="prince_philip28@yahoo.com my" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Return-Path" content="&lt;prince_philip28@yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="RO" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Multipart-Boundary" content="0-1183065902-1088752552=:51796" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Fri Jul  2 03:15:55 2004" />
<meta name="MboxParser-return-path" content="&lt;prince_philip28@yahoo.com&gt; " />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Message-ID" content="&lt;20040702071553.54280.qmail@web54008.mail.yahoo.com&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="APPRECIATION!" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0 government who are bent&lt;BR&gt;on taking everything&lt;BR&gt;we have got. Since the South African government&lt;BR&gt;seems to be playing&lt;BR&gt;along with them, I am now faced with the dilemma of&lt;BR&gt;moving this fund out&lt;BR&gt;of South Africa for fear of going through the same&lt;BR&gt;experience in future&lt;BR&gt;because both countries have similar political&lt;BR&gt;history.&lt;BR&gt;As a businessman, I am seeking for a partner who I&lt;BR&gt;have to entrust my&lt;BR&gt;future and that of my family in his hands, I must&lt;BR&gt;let you know that this&lt;BR&gt;transaction is risk free. If you accept to assist me&lt;BR&gt;and my family all I&lt;BR&gt;want you to do for me, is to make an arrangements&lt;BR&gt;with the security&lt;BR&gt;company to clear the consignment (funds) from their&lt;BR&gt;affiliate office&lt;BR&gt;here in the Netherlands as i have already given&lt;BR&gt;directives for the&lt;BR&gt;consignment to be brought to the Netherlands from&lt;BR&gt;South Africa. But&lt;BR&gt;before then all modalities will have to be put in&lt;BR&gt;place like change of&lt;BR&gt;ownership to the consignment and more" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Multipart-Subtype" content="alternative" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-965" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="dc:identifier" content="&lt;20040702071553.54280.qmail@web54008.mail.yahoo.com&gt; Land" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<title>APPRECIATION!</title>
</head>
<body>

With good faith i have come to you on this proposal
which i feel you
are liable of handling, and firstly i must introduce myself,i am PRINCE PHILIP
GARBI, the first son and manager of Mr. Garbi
Thembe, one of the most
popular black farmers in Zimbabwe who was recently
murdered in the land
dispute in my country.
I got your contact through network online hence
decided to write you,
Before the death of my father, he took me to
Johannesburg to deposit the
sum of US29 million ( twenty-nine million, 
United States
dollars), in one of the private security company, as
he foresaw the
looming danger in Zimbabwe, this money was deposited
in a box as family
valuables to avoid much demurrage from security
company. This amount was
meant for the purchase of new machines and chemicals
for a new Farm
establishment in Swaziland.
This land problem came when Zimbabwean President
Mr.Robert Mugabe
introduced a new 
 Land
 Reform Act wholly affecting
the rich white farmers
and some few black farmers, and this resulted to the
killing and mobbing
by Zimbabwean war veterans and some lunatics in the
society. In fact a
lot of people were killed because of this Land
reform Act of which my
father was one of the victims.
It is against this background that, my family and I
fled Zimbabwe for
fear of our lives and are currently staying in the
Netherlands where we
are seeking political asylum and more so have
decided to transfer my
father's fund to a more reliable foreign account,
Since the law of
Netherlands prohibits a refugee (asylum seeker) to
open any bank account
or to be involved in any financial transaction
throughout the
Territorial zone of Netherlands.
As the eldest son of my father, I am saddled with
the responsibility of
seeking a genuine foreign account where this money
could be transferred
without the knowledge of 
 my
 government who are bent
on taking everything
we have got. Since the South African government
seems to be playing
along with them, I am now faced with the dilemma of
moving this fund out
of South Africa for fear of going through the same
experience in future
because both countries have similar political
history.
As a businessman, I am seeking for a partner who I
have to entrust my
future and that of my family in his hands, I must
let you know that this
transaction is risk free. If you accept to assist me
and my family all I
want you to do for me, is to make an arrangements
with the security
company to clear the consignment (funds) from their
affiliate office
here in the Netherlands as i have already given
directives for the
consignment to be brought to the Netherlands from
South Africa. But
before then all modalities will have to be put in
place like change of
ownership to the consignment and more
 importantly
this money I intend to
use for investment.
I have two options for you. Firstly you can choose
to have certain
percentage of the money for nominating your account
for this
transaction. Or you can go into partnership with me
for a proper
profitable investment in your country. Whichever
option you want, feel
free to notify me. I have also mapped out 5% of this
money for all kinds
of expenses incured in the process of this
transaction. If you do not
prefer a partnership I am willing to give you 10% of
the money while the
remaining 85% will be for my investment in your
country. Contact me with
the E-mail address while I implore you to maintain
the absolute secrecy
required in this transaction. Thanks, God bless you.

Yours faithfully,
PRINCE PHILIP  GARBI


<p>
		</p>


Do you Yahoo!?

<a shape="rect" href="http://us.rd.yahoo.com/mail_us/taglines/10/*http://promotions.yahoo.com/new_mail/static/efficiency.html">New and Improved Yahoo! Mail</a> - Send 10MB messages!</body></html>