<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<meta name="subject" content="Reply ASAP..." />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="&quot;Dr (Mrs) BETTY PEDRO&quot; &lt;betty_pedro01@jumpy.it&gt;" />
<meta name="dc:creator" content="Dr (Mrs) BETTY PEDRO &lt;betty_pedro01@jumpy.it&gt;" />
<meta name="MboxParser-status" content="O" />
<meta name="MboxParser-tel" content="234-80-433-21216," />
<meta name="Message:From-Email" content="betty_pedro01@jumpy.it" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="betty_pedro01@jumpy.it" />
<meta name="Message-To" content="betty_pedro01@jumpy.it" />
<meta name="dc:format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;ISO-8859-15&quot;" />
<meta name="Message-Recipient-Address" content="betty_pedro01@jumpy.it" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Status" content="O" />
<meta name="MboxParser-reply-to" content="betty_pedro3@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:MIME-Version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="dc:title" content="Reply ASAP..." />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Reply-To" content="betty_pedro3@yahoo.com" />
<meta name="Content-Type-Override" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="Content-Type" content="message/rfc822" />
<meta name="MboxParser-content-transfer-encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="creator" content="&quot;Dr (Mrs) BETTY PEDRO&quot; &lt;betty_pedro01@jumpy.it&gt;" />
<meta name="creator" content="Dr (Mrs) BETTY PEDRO &lt;betty_pedro01@jumpy.it&gt;" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.DefaultParser" />
<meta name="X-Parsed-By" content="org.apache.tika.parser.mail.RFC822Parser" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Type" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;ISO-8859-15&quot;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="&quot;Dr (Mrs) BETTY PEDRO&quot; &lt;betty_pedro01@jumpy.it&gt;" />
<meta name="meta:author" content="Dr (Mrs) BETTY PEDRO &lt;betty_pedro01@jumpy.it&gt;" />
<meta name="format" content="text/plain; charset=&quot;ISO-8859-15&quot;" />
<meta name="Message:Raw-Header:Content-Transfer-Encoding" content="quoted-printable" />
<meta name="MboxParser-attn" content="MD/CEO" />
<meta name="MboxParser-from" content="r  Sun Jul  4 11:09:34 2004" />
<meta name="MboxParser-mime-version" content="1.0" />
<meta name="Message:From-Name" content="Dr (Mrs) BETTY PEDRO" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_depth" content="1" />
<meta name="Author" content="&quot;Dr (Mrs) BETTY PEDRO&quot; &lt;betty_pedro01@jumpy.it&gt;" />
<meta name="Author" content="Dr (Mrs) BETTY PEDRO &lt;betty_pedro01@jumpy.it&gt;" />
<meta name="X-TIKA:embedded_resource_path" content="/embedded-972" />
<meta name="Message-From" content="Dr (Mrs) BETTY PEDRO &lt;betty_pedro01@jumpy.it&gt;" />
<title>Reply ASAP...</title>
</head>
<body><p>Dr.(Mrs)Betty Pedro
Diamond Bank Plc
ILupeju Branch,
Lagos, Nigeria.
TEL: 234-80-433-21216,

ATTN: MD/CEO

I am Dr.(Mrs)Betty Pedro, Branch Manager Diamond Bank Plc,ILupeju Branch,
Lagos,  Nigeria.

I have an urgent and very profitable business proposition for you that should
be handled with extreme confidentiality.

On January 6,1998 a Foreign  Consultant and contractor with the Nigerian
Water Corporation Mr. Marc Smith Pena by name made a numbered time Fixed
Deposit for twelve calendar months valued at US$40.9M(fourty Million, Nine
Hundred thousand United States Dollars Only) in my branch.

Upon maturity I sent a routine notification in accordance with the Bank
policy to his forwarding address but got no reply.
After a month we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract
employers Nigerian Water Corporation that Mr. Marc Smith Pena died from
an automobile accident.

On further investigation, we found out that he died without making a Will
and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless.
I therefore made further investigations and discovered that Mr. Marc Smith
Pena  did not declare any next of kin or relations in all his official documents
including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank.
This sum of US$40.9M has been carefully  moved out of my bank to a Financial
and Security Company in Europe for safekeeping.

No one will ever come forward to claim it and according to the Law of my
country, at the expiration of 7 years the money will revert to the ownership
of the State (Government) if nobody applies to claim the fund.

We decided to contact you to receive his money and investments on his behalf
as everything will be taken over by the government as provided in section
129 sub 63(N), Nigerian Banking Edit of 1961.
This prompted us to contact you.We want to front you as the next of kin
of our late client thereby making you the legal beneficiary of the sum of
$40.9 million U.S Dollars that is presently in a Financial and Security
Company in Europe.

I contacted you because it is against the civil service code of ethics to
own and operate foreign accounts and your assistance would be needed to
claim the money in the Financial and Security Company in Europe,which also
has branches in Asia.

We have unanimously agreed that 35% of the entire sum would be for you if
you agree to take part in this profitable transaction,55% for me while the
remaining 10% would be used to pay back the expenses that may be incurred
during the course of the transaction by both parties after the fund has
been claimed and lodged in your account.

In the event that you are genuinely interested in the transaction, the following
information would be needed from you to expedite action.
1) Your Full Name .
2) Your Residential or Company Address.
3) Your Private Mobile,Telphone and Fax numbers where you can be reached
at all time because this transaction entails constant communication.

The transaction is 100% legal and totally free of risks as all modalities
has been perfected to ensure the hitch free success of the transaction.

If you are interested, send the requested information via email as soon
as possible so that we can proceed and after sending it you call me.
I await your response urgently.
Regards,
Dr.(Mrs)Betty Pedro


________________________________________
Tutti i concerti da non perdere! http://musica.jumpy.it/2003jm_m_concerti.asp


</p>

</body></html>